{
	"description": "Obscure kanji with strange readings",
	"deck": [
		{ "question": "丁尼生", "answers": [ "テニソン" ]},
		{ "question": "丁抹", "answers": [ "デンマーク" ], "comment": "Denmark" },
		{ "question": "丁蘭", "answers": [ "テヘラン" ]},
		{ "question": "七星瓢虫", "answers": [ "ななほしてんとう" ], "comment": "seven-spot ladybird; seven-spotted ladybug (Coccinella septempunctata)" },
		{ "question": "七節", "answers": [ "ななふし" ], "comment": "walking stick (any insect of order Phasmatodea); walkingstick; stick insect; leaf insect" },
		{ "question": "万寿果", "answers": [ "パパイア" ]},
		{ "question": "三和土", "answers": [ "たたき" ], "comment": "hard-packed dirt (clay, gravel, etc.) floor; concrete floor" },
		{ "question": "三鞭酒", "answers": [ "シャンペン" ], "comment": "Champagne" },
		{ "question": "不如帰", "answers": [ "ほととぎす" ], "comment": "lesser cuckoo (Cuculus poliocephalus)" },
		{ "question": "乾蒸餅", "answers": [ "ビスケット" ]},
		{ "question": "乾酪", "answers": [ "チーズ" ], "comment": "cheese" },
		{ "question": "亀虫", "answers": [ "かめむし" ], "comment": "shield bug; stink bug" },
		{ "question": "井守", "answers": [ "いもり" ], "comment": "newt (esp. the Japanese fire belly newt, Cynops pyrrhogaster)" },
		{ "question": "亜剌比亜", "answers": [ "アラビア" ], "comment": "Arabia" },
		{ "question": "亜弗掩担", "answers": [ "アフガニスタン" ]},
		{ "question": "亜武的達", "answers": [ "アムステルダム" ]},
		{ "question": "亜歴山特", "answers": [ "アレクサンドリア" ]},
		{ "question": "亜爾加里", "answers": [ "アルカリ" ]},
		{ "question": "亜爾然丁", "answers": [ "アルゼンチン" ], "comment": "Argentina" },
		{ "question": "亜米利加", "answers": [ "アメリカ" ], "comment": "America\nUnited States of America" },
		{ "question": "亜細亜", "answers": [ "アジア" ], "comment": "Asia (esp. \"the Far East\")\nAsian; Asiatic" },
		{ "question": "亜馬生", "answers": [ "アマゾン" ]},
		{ "question": "交譲葉", "answers": [ "ゆずりは" ]},
		{ "question": "人参", "answers": [ "にんじん" ], "comment": "carrot (Daucus carota)\nAsian ginseng (Panax ginseng)" },
		{ "question": "人手", "answers": [ "ひとで" ], "comment": "starfish; sea star; asteroid; any echinoderm of the class Asteroidea\nnorthern Pacific seastar (Asterias amurensis)\nsomeone else's hands; other hands\nhand (worker); aide\nlabor; work; manpower; effort\nhelp; assistance" },
		{ "question": "仏法僧", "answers": [ "ぶっぽうそう" ], "comment": "Buddha, Dharma, Sangha; The Three Jewels; Buddha, the teachings of Buddha, and the community of monks and nuns\ndollarbird (Eurystomus orientalis)\nroller (any bird of family Coraciidae)\nEurasian scops owl (Otus scops)" },
		{ "question": "仏蘭西", "answers": [ "フランス" ], "comment": "France" },
		{ "question": "仙人掌", "answers": [ "さぼてん" ], "comment": "cactus" },
		{ "question": "仮漆", "answers": [ "ニス" ], "comment": "varnish" },
		{ "question": "仲人", "answers": [ "なこうど" ], "comment": "matchmaker\ngo-between; intermediary; middleman; mediator; intercessor\ngo-between; matchmaker" },
		{ "question": "伊太利", "answers": [ "イタリア" ], "comment": "Italy" },
		{ "question": "伊色剌", "answers": [ "イスラエル" ]},
		{ "question": "伯剌西爾", "answers": [ "ブラジル" ], "comment": "Brazil" },
		{ "question": "伯林", "answers": [ "ベルリン" ], "comment": "Berlin" },
		{ "question": "伯理", "answers": [ "ペリー" ]},
		{ "question": "但丁", "answers": [ "ダンテ" ]},
		{ "question": "佛羅里達", "answers": [ "フロリダ" ]},
		{ "question": "佛蘭格林", "answers": [ "フランクリン" ]},
		{ "question": "保羅", "answers": [ "パウロ" ]},
		{ "question": "信天翁", "answers": [ "あほうどり" ], "comment": "albatross (esp. the short-tailed albatross, Phoebastria albatrus)" },
		{ "question": "倍根", "answers": [ "ベーコン" ]},
		{ "question": "倍良", "answers": [ "べら" ], "comment": "wrasse (any fish of family Labridae)" },
		{ "question": "倍諾愛勒", "answers": [ "ブエノスアイレス" ]},
		{ "question": "倫敦", "answers": [ "ロンドン" ], "comment": "London" },
		{ "question": "倶楽部", "answers": [ "クラブ" ], "comment": "club; fraternity; sorority; clubhouse" },
		{ "question": "儒艮", "answers": [ "じゅごん" ], "comment": "dugong (Dugong dugon); sea pig" },
		{ "question": "克利奥佩特剌", "answers": [ "クレオパトラ" ]},
		{ "question": "兎", "answers": [ "うさぎ" ], "comment": "rabbit; hare; coney; cony; lagomorph (esp. leporids)" },
		{ "question": "兜虫", "answers": [ "かぶとむし" ], "comment": "rhinoceros beetle (esp. the Japanese rhinoceros beetle, Trypoxylus dichotomus)" },
		{ "question": "兜蝦", "answers": [ "かぶとえび" ], "comment": "tadpole shrimp (Triopsidae spp.); shield shrimp" },
		{ "question": "兜蟹", "answers": [ "かぶとがに" ], "comment": "horseshoe crab" },
		{ "question": "八重葎", "answers": [ "やえむぐら" ], "comment": "thick patch of mixed weeds\nfalse cleavers (species of bedstraw, Galium spurium var. echinospermon)" },
		{ "question": "公孫樹", "answers": [ "いちょう" ], "comment": "ginkgo (Ginkgo biloba); gingko; maidenhair tree" },
		{ "question": "公果", "answers": [ "コンゴ" ]},
		{ "question": "公魚", "answers": [ "わかさぎ" ], "comment": "Japanese pond smelt (Hypomesus nipponensis)" },
		{ "question": "円規", "answers": [ "コンパス" ], "comment": "pair of compasses" },
		{ "question": "冬瓜", "answers": [ "とうがん" ], "comment": "wax gourd (Benincasa hispida); ash gourd; white gourd; winter melon" },
		{ "question": "冬眠鼠", "answers": [ "やまね" ], "comment": "Japanese dormouse (Glirulus japonicus)" },
		{ "question": "凝乳", "answers": [ "クリーム" ], "comment": "curd; curds; curdled milk" },
		{ "question": "切支丹", "answers": [ "キリシタン" ], "comment": "early Japanese Christianity (from the later Muromachi period); early Japanese Christian" },
		{ "question": "列寧", "answers": [ "レーニン" ], "comment": "Lenin" },
		{ "question": "利比亜", "answers": [ "リビア" ], "comment": "Libya" },
		{ "question": "刷毛", "answers": [ "ブラシ" ], "comment": "brush (e.g. for painting, basting, etc.); whisk" },
		{ "question": "剃刀", "answers": [ "かみそり" ], "comment": "razor" },
		{ "question": "剣橋", "answers": [ "ケンブリッジ" ], "comment": "Cambridge" },
		{ "question": "剪刀", "answers": [ "はさみ" ], "comment": "scissors (esp. surgical scissors)\nscissors; shears; clippers\nhole punch" },
		{ "question": "剽軽", "answers": [ "ひょうきん" ], "comment": "facetious; droll; funny" },
		{ "question": "加加阿", "answers": [ "カカオ" ]},
		{ "question": "加奈陀", "answers": [ "カナダ" ], "comment": "Canada" },
		{ "question": "加特力", "answers": [ "カトリック" ], "comment": "Catholic (church)" },
		{ "question": "加留多", "answers": [ "カルタ" ], "comment": "karuta; traditional Japanese playing cards" },
		{ "question": "加答児", "answers": [ "カタル" ], "comment": "catarrh" },
		{ "question": "加里", "answers": [ "カリ" ], "comment": "potassium\npotash" },
		{ "question": "加里保爾尼", "answers": [ "カリフォルニア" ]},
		{ "question": "勃牙利", "answers": [ "ブルガリア" ], "comment": "Bulgaria" },
		{ "question": "勺旁", "answers": [ "ショパン" ]},
		{ "question": "勿忘草", "answers": [ "わすれなぐさ" ], "comment": "forget-me-not (esp. the water forget-me-not, Myosotis scorpioides)" },
		{ "question": "匈牙利", "answers": [ "ハンガリー" ], "comment": "Hungary" },
		{ "question": "千鳥", "answers": [ "ちどり" ], "comment": "plover" },
		{ "question": "午睡", "answers": [ "ひるね" ], "comment": "nap; siesta" },
		{ "question": "卓別麟", "answers": [ "チャップリン" ]},
		{ "question": "卓子", "answers": [ "テーブル" ], "comment": "table" },
		{ "question": "南瓜", "answers": [ "かぼちゃ" ], "comment": "pumpkin (Cucurbita sp.); squash" },
		{ "question": "印度", "answers": [ "インド" ], "comment": "India" },
		{ "question": "双六", "answers": [ "すごろく" ], "comment": "sugoroku; traditional Japanese board game played with dice" },
		{ "question": "双陸", "answers": [ "すごろく" ], "comment": "sugoroku; traditional Japanese board game played with dice" },
		{ "question": "叔伯特", "answers": [ "シューベルト" ]},
		{ "question": "口風琴", "answers": [ "ハーモニカ" ]},
		{ "question": "古倫母", "answers": [ "コロンボ" ]},
		{ "question": "吃逆", "answers": [ "しゃっくり" ], "comment": "hiccough; hiccup" },
		{ "question": "吃驚", "answers": [ "びっくり" ], "comment": "to be surprised; to be amazed; to be frightened; to be astonished; to get startled; to jump\nsurprise (e.g. surprise party)\nsurprise" },
		{ "question": "合歓木", "answers": [ "ねむのき" ], "comment": "silk tree (Albizia julibrissin)" },
		{ "question": "合羽", "answers": [ "カッパ" ], "comment": "raincoat" },
		{ "question": "吉丁虫", "answers": [ "たまむし" ], "comment": "jewel beetle; Chrysochroa fulgidissima; insect with iridescent wings" },
		{ "question": "向日葵", "answers": [ "ひまわり" ], "comment": "sunflower (Helianthus annuus)" },
		{ "question": "君府", "answers": [ "コンスタンチノープル" ]},
		{ "question": "吹螺", "answers": [ "ほらがい" ], "comment": "conch (esp. Charonia tritonis); trumpet shell" },
		{ "question": "告天子", "answers": [ "ひばり" ], "comment": "skylark (Alauda arvensis)\nMongolian lark (Melanocorypha mongolica)" },
		{ "question": "和布", "answers": [ "わかめ" ], "comment": "wakame (species of edible brown seaweed, Undaria pinnatifida)" },
		{ "question": "和蘭", "answers": [ "オランダ" ], "comment": "Holland; The Netherlands" },
		{ "question": "哥倫比亜", "answers": [ "コロンビア" ], "comment": "Colombia" },
		{ "question": "哨吶", "answers": [ "チャルメラ" ], "comment": "shawm-like instrument played by street vendors (sometimes referred to as a flute)\nsuona (Chinese shawm)" },
		{ "question": "唐松", "answers": [ "からまつ" ], "comment": "(Japanese) larch (Larix leptolepis, Larix kaempferi)" },
		{ "question": "唐檜", "answers": [ "とうひ" ], "comment": "spruce tree (esp. Picea jezoensis hondoensis, a variety of Ezo spruce)" },
		{ "question": "唐縮緬", "answers": [ "メリンス" ], "comment": "mousseline de laine; mousseline; light woollen fabric" },
		{ "question": "唐辛子", "answers": [ "とうがらし" ], "comment": "capsicum (Capsicum annuum, esp. the cultivated chili peppers); chili pepper (chile, chilli); cayenne; red pepper\nshichimi pepper" },
		{ "question": "啄木鳥", "answers": [ "きつつき" ], "comment": "woodpecker" },
		{ "question": "商人", "answers": [ "あきんど" ], "comment": "trader; shopkeeper; merchant" },
		{ "question": "喇叭", "answers": [ "ラッパ" ], "comment": "trumpet; horn; bugle" },
		{ "question": "喜馬拉雅", "answers": [ "ヒマラヤ" ]},
		{ "question": "喞筒", "answers": [ "ポンプ" ], "comment": "pump" },
		{ "question": "喫驚", "answers": [ "びっくり" ], "comment": "to be surprised; to be amazed; to be frightened; to be astonished; to get startled; to jump\nsurprise (e.g. surprise party)\nsurprise" },
		{ "question": "嗽", "answers": [ "うがい" ], "comment": "gargling; rinsing one's mouth" },
		{ "question": "嘉魚", "answers": [ "いわな" ], "comment": "char; charr" },
		{ "question": "嚔", "answers": [ "くしゃみ" ], "comment": "sneeze\nspoken twice in response to someone sneezing as a charm against an early death" },
		{ "question": "四十雀", "answers": [ "しじゅうから" ], "comment": "great tit (Parus major)" },
		{ "question": "回青橙", "answers": [ "だいだい" ]},
		{ "question": "団子虫", "answers": [ "だんごむし" ], "comment": "pillbug; pill bug; woodlouse; sowbug; sow bug; slater" },
		{ "question": "団栗", "answers": [ "どんぐり" ], "comment": "acorn" },
		{ "question": "土瀝青", "answers": [ "アスファルト" ], "comment": "asphalt" },
		{ "question": "土竜", "answers": [ "もぐら" ], "comment": "mole (Talpidae spp., esp. the small Japanese mole, Mogera imaizumii)" },
		{ "question": "土筆", "answers": [ "つくし" ], "comment": "fertile shoot of field horsetail\nwooden stick with a burned tip (used to create underdrawings)" },
		{ "question": "土耳古", "answers": [ "トルコ" ], "comment": "Turkey\nturquoise" },
		{ "question": "地潜", "answers": [ "じむぐり" ], "comment": "Japanese forest rat snake (Euprepiophis conspicillatus, Elaphe conspicillata); burrowing rat snake" },
		{ "question": "坩堝", "answers": [ "るつぼ" ], "comment": "crucible; (melting) pot" },
		{ "question": "型録", "answers": [ "カタログ" ], "comment": "catalog; catalogue" },
		{ "question": "埃", "answers": [ "ほこり" ], "comment": "dust\none ten-billionth" },
		{ "question": "埃及", "answers": [ "エジプト" ], "comment": "Egypt" },
		{ "question": "堅魚", "answers": [ "かつお" ], "comment": "skipjack tuna (Katsuwonus pelamis); oceanic bonito; victorfish" },
		{ "question": "報達", "answers": [ "バグダッド" ]},
		{ "question": "塩辛蜻蛉", "answers": [ "しおからとんぼ" ], "comment": "Orthetrum albistylum speciosum (subspecies of white-tailed skimmer)" },
		{ "question": "塵箱", "answers": [ "ごみばこ" ], "comment": "garbage can; garbage box; rubbish bin; trash can; dust bin; dustbin" },
		{ "question": "塵芥虫", "answers": [ "ごみむし" ], "comment": "ground beetle; carabid (esp. of superfamily Caraboidea, but excluding subfamily Carabinae)\nAnisodactylus signatus (species of ground beetle)" },
		{ "question": "墓利比亜", "answers": [ "ボリビア" ]},
		{ "question": "墨西哥", "answers": [ "メキシコ" ], "comment": "Mexico" },
		{ "question": "墺太利", "answers": [ "オーストリア" ], "comment": "Austria" },
		{ "question": "壁蝨", "answers": [ "だに" ], "comment": "tick (Acari spp.); mite" },
		{ "question": "士篤恒", "answers": [ "ストックホルム" ]},
		{ "question": "多倫多", "answers": [ "トロント" ]},
		{ "question": "夜鷹", "answers": [ "よたか" ], "comment": "grey nightjar (Caprimulgus indicus)\nnightjar (any bird of family Caprimulgidae); goatsucker\nstreetwalker; low class prostitute (Edo period)\nsoba vendors who walk around at night; soba sold by these vendors" },
		{ "question": "大口魚", "answers": [ "たら" ], "comment": "gadid (any fish of the family Gadidae, incl. cod, haddock, whiting and pollack)\nPacific cod (Gadus macrocephalus)" },
		{ "question": "大胡麻斑蝶", "answers": [ "おおごまだら" ], "comment": "tree nymph butterfly (Idea leuconoe)" },
		{ "question": "大葉子", "answers": [ "おおばこ" ], "comment": "plantain (esp. Asian plantain, Plantago asiatica)" },
		{ "question": "大蒜", "answers": [ "にんにく" ], "comment": "garlic (Allium sativum)" },
		{ "question": "大角豆", "answers": [ "ささげ" ], "comment": "cowpea (Vigna unguiculata); cow pea; black-eyed pea; southern pea" },
		{ "question": "大鷭", "answers": [ "おおばん" ], "comment": "coot (Fulica atra)" },
		{ "question": "天牛", "answers": [ "かみきりむし" ], "comment": "long-horned beetle" },
		{ "question": "天竺牡丹", "answers": [ "ダリア" ], "comment": "dahlia" },
		{ "question": "天道虫", "answers": [ "てんとうむし" ], "comment": "ladybug (Harmonia axyridis); ladybird" },
		{ "question": "天鵞絨", "answers": [ "ビロード" ], "comment": "velvet" },
		{ "question": "天麩羅", "answers": [ "テンプラ" ], "comment": "tempura; deep-fried fish and vegetables in a light batter" },
		{ "question": "太刀魚", "answers": [ "たちうお" ], "comment": "largehead hairtail (Trichiurus lepturus); scabbard fish; beltfish" },
		{ "question": "女郎花", "answers": [ "おみなえし" ], "comment": "golden lace (Patrinia scabiosifolia); scabious patrinia; yellow patrinia" },
		{ "question": "如雨露", "answers": [ "ジョウロ" ], "comment": "watering can; watering pot; sprinkling can" },
		{ "question": "威内斯", "answers": [ "ベニス" ]},
		{ "question": "媒人", "answers": [ "なこうど" ], "comment": "matchmaker\ngo-between; intermediary; middleman; mediator; intercessor" },
		{ "question": "子規", "answers": [ "ほととぎす" ], "comment": "lesser cuckoo (Cuculus poliocephalus)" },
		{ "question": "孑孑", "answers": [ "ぼうふら" ], "comment": "mosquito larva; wriggler; maggot" },
		{ "question": "孔雀", "answers": [ "くじゃく" ], "comment": "peafowl (incl. the male peacock, female peahen, and young peachick)" },
		{ "question": "孟徳斯鳩", "answers": [ "モンテスキュー" ]},
		{ "question": "宇柳具", "answers": [ "ウルグアイ" ]},
		{ "question": "守宮", "answers": [ "やもり" ], "comment": "gecko; house lizard\noutcasts common around the Kyoto region from the Kamakura period to the Edo period" },
		{ "question": "安南", "answers": [ "アンナン" ], "comment": "Annam; old name of Vietnam" },
		{ "question": "客", "answers": [ "まろうど" ], "comment": "guest; visitor\ncustomer; client; shopper; spectator; audience; tourist; sightseer; passenger\nvisitor from afar; guest\nvisitor from afar\njoy-bringing spirit from the divine realms" },
		{ "question": "客人", "answers": [ "まろうど" ], "comment": "caller; visitor; company; guest\nvisitor from afar; guest\nvisitor from afar\njoy-bringing spirit from the divine realms" },
		{ "question": "家守", "answers": [ "やもり" ], "comment": "gecko; house lizard" },
		{ "question": "家鴨", "answers": [ "あひる" ], "comment": "domestic duck" },
		{ "question": "宿借り", "answers": [ "やどかり" ], "comment": "hermit crab\nrenting a house\ntenant" },
		{ "question": "寄居虫", "answers": [ "やどかり" ], "comment": "hermit crab" },
		{ "question": "密爾敦", "answers": [ "ミルトン" ]},
		{ "question": "富士壺", "answers": [ "ふじつぼ" ], "comment": "acorn barnacle (Balanomorpha spp.)" },
		{ "question": "寿府", "answers": [ "ジュネーブ" ], "comment": "Geneva" },
		{ "question": "小啄木鳥", "answers": [ "こげら" ], "comment": "pygmy woodpecker (Dendrocopos kizuki)" },
		{ "question": "小楢", "answers": [ "こなら" ], "comment": "konara oak (Quercus serrata); pin oak" },
		{ "question": "小田羽", "answers": [ "オタワ" ]},
		{ "question": "小酒", "answers": [ "リキュール" ]},
		{ "question": "尺取虫", "answers": [ "しゃくとりむし" ], "comment": "inchworm; measuring worm; looper (caterpillar)" },
		{ "question": "尼加拉瓦", "answers": [ "ニカラグア" ], "comment": "Nicaragua" },
		{ "question": "尼哇達", "answers": [ "ネバダ" ]},
		{ "question": "尼通", "answers": [ "ニュートン" ]},
		{ "question": "居利", "answers": [ "キュリー" ]},
		{ "question": "山原水鶏", "answers": [ "やんばるくいな" ], "comment": "Okinawa rail (Gallirallus okinawae)" },
		{ "question": "山女", "answers": [ "やまめ" ], "comment": "landlocked masu salmon (Oncorhynchus masou masou)\nmountain witch\nakebia (Akebia quinata)" },
		{ "question": "山女魚", "answers": [ "やまめ" ], "comment": "landlocked masu salmon (Oncorhynchus masou masou)" },
		{ "question": "山梔子", "answers": [ "くちなし" ], "comment": "Cape jasmine (Gardenia jasminoides); Cape jessamine; gardenia\ngardenia fruit" },
		{ "question": "山椒", "answers": [ "さんしょう" ], "comment": "Japanese pepper (species of Sichuan pepper, Zanthoxylum piperitum); Japanese prickly ash" },
		{ "question": "山椒魚", "answers": [ "さんしょううお" ], "comment": "salamander" },
		{ "question": "山楝蛇", "answers": [ "やまかがし" ]},
		{ "question": "山羊", "answers": [ "やぎ" ], "comment": "goat" },
		{ "question": "山翡翠", "answers": [ "やませみ" ], "comment": "crested kingfisher (Megaceryle lugubris)" },
		{ "question": "山茶花", "answers": [ "さざんか" ], "comment": "sasanqua (Camellia sasanqua)" },
		{ "question": "山荒", "answers": [ "やまあらし" ], "comment": "porcupine (any mammal of suborder Hystricomorpha)" },
		{ "question": "山葵", "answers": [ "わさび" ], "comment": "wasabi (Wasabia japonica)" },
		{ "question": "山魚狗", "answers": [ "やませみ" ], "comment": "crested kingfisher (Megaceryle lugubris)" },
		{ "question": "山鼠", "answers": [ "やまね" ], "comment": "Japanese dormouse (Glirulus japonicus)" },
		{ "question": "岩魚", "answers": [ "いわな" ], "comment": "char; charr" },
		{ "question": "川獺", "answers": [ "かわうそ" ], "comment": "otter (Lutra lutra)\nJapanese river otter (Lutra lutra whiteleyi)" },
		{ "question": "川蜷", "answers": [ "かわにな" ]},
		{ "question": "川蝉", "answers": [ "かわせみ" ], "comment": "kingfisher (esp. the common kingfisher, Alcedo atthis)\njade (gem)\nbeautiful lustrous colour similar to that of the kingfisher's feathers" },
		{ "question": "差羽", "answers": [ "さしば" ], "comment": "grey-faced buzzard (Butastur indicus); gray-faced buzzard" },
		{ "question": "巴哈", "answers": [ "バッハ" ]},
		{ "question": "巴奈馬", "answers": [ "パナマ" ], "comment": "Panama" },
		{ "question": "巴羅貝", "answers": [ "パラグアイ" ]},
		{ "question": "巴里", "answers": [ "パリ" ], "comment": "Paris (France)" },
		{ "question": "巴黎", "answers": [ "パリ" ]},
		{ "question": "巵子", "answers": [ "くちなし" ], "comment": "Cape jasmine (Gardenia jasminoides); Cape jessamine; gardenia" },
		{ "question": "巻耳", "answers": [ "おなもみ" ], "comment": "cocklebur (Xanthium strumarium); cockleburr" },
		{ "question": "市俄古", "answers": [ "シカゴ" ]},
		{ "question": "布哇", "answers": [ "ハワイ" ], "comment": "Hawaii" },
		{ "question": "布団", "answers": [ "ふとん" ], "comment": "futon (quilted Japanese-style mattress laid out on the floor)\nround cushion used for Zen meditation (traditionally made of woven bulrush leaves)" },
		{ "question": "帆檣", "answers": [ "マスト" ], "comment": "mast" },
		{ "question": "帆立貝", "answers": [ "ほたてがい" ], "comment": "Japanese scallop (Patinopecten yessoensis); Yesso scallop" },
		{ "question": "希臘", "answers": [ "ギリシャ" ], "comment": "Greece" },
		{ "question": "帚", "answers": [ "ほうき" ], "comment": "broom" },
		{ "question": "帷子", "answers": [ "かたびら" ], "comment": "light, thin, single-layer kimono (esp. from hemp or raw silk, for summer use)\nshroud; burial clothes" },
		{ "question": "平目", "answers": [ "ひらめ" ], "comment": "flounder (esp. the large-tooth flounders of family Paralichthyidae, but also lefteye flounders of family Bothidae)\nbastard halibut; olive flounder (Paralichthys olivaceus)" },
		{ "question": "年魚", "answers": [ "あゆ" ], "comment": "sweetfish (Plecoglossus altivelis altivelis); ayu\nsalmon" },
		{ "question": "幾肉亜", "answers": [ "ギニア" ]},
		{ "question": "庭球", "answers": [ "テニス" ], "comment": "tennis" },
		{ "question": "康徳", "answers": [ "カント" ]},
		{ "question": "弥撒", "answers": [ "ミサ" ]},
		{ "question": "弾機", "answers": [ "ばね" ], "comment": "spring (e.g. coil, leaf); mainspring; power spring" },
		{ "question": "彼得格勒", "answers": [ "ペトログラード" ]},
		{ "question": "得撒", "answers": [ "テキサス" ]},
		{ "question": "御歯黒", "answers": [ "おはぐろ" ], "comment": "tooth blackening\ntooth-blackening dye" },
		{ "question": "御玉杓子", "answers": [ "おたまじゃくし" ], "comment": "ladle\ntadpole\nmusical note" },
		{ "question": "微塵子", "answers": [ "みじんこ" ], "comment": "water flea (Daphnia spp.)" },
		{ "question": "心太", "answers": [ "ところてん" ], "comment": "gelidium jelly strips (made from agar-agar)\nprostate orgasm" },
		{ "question": "快速船", "answers": [ "ヨット" ], "comment": "fast ship" },
		{ "question": "忽布", "answers": [ "ホップ" ]},
		{ "question": "思格尓", "answers": [ "エンゲルス" ]},
		{ "question": "怪我", "answers": [ "けが" ], "comment": "injury (to animate object); hurt" },
		{ "question": "怪鴟", "answers": [ "よたか" ], "comment": "grey nightjar (Caprimulgus indicus)\nnightjar (any bird of family Caprimulgidae); goatsucker" },
		{ "question": "恙虫", "answers": [ "つつがむし" ], "comment": "chigger; jigger; harvest mite (any mite of family Trombiculidae)" },
		{ "question": "悉徳尼", "answers": [ "シドニー" ]},
		{ "question": "愛斯蘭", "answers": [ "アイスランド" ], "comment": "Iceland" },
		{ "question": "愛蘭", "answers": [ "アイルランド" ], "comment": "Ireland; Eire" },
		{ "question": "愛迪生", "answers": [ "エジソン" ]},
		{ "question": "懸巣", "answers": [ "かけす" ], "comment": "Eurasian jay (Garrulus glandarius)" },
		{ "question": "戈", "answers": [ "ほこ" ], "comment": "long-handled Chinese spear; lance; pike\nweapon; arms\ngrip of a bow\nge (ancient Chinese dagger-axe)" },
		{ "question": "戈壁", "answers": [ "ゴビ" ]},
		{ "question": "成吉思汗", "answers": [ "チンギスハン" ], "comment": "Japanese mutton and vegetable dish; slotted dome cast iron grill for preparing this dish" },
		{ "question": "我儘", "answers": [ "わがまま" ], "comment": "selfishness; egoism; self-indulgence; wilfulness; willfulness\ndisobedience\nwhim" },
		{ "question": "戟", "answers": [ "ほこ" ], "comment": "long-handled Chinese spear; lance; pike\nweapon; arms\ngrip of a bow\nji (ancient Chinese halberd)" },
		{ "question": "戴勝", "answers": [ "やつがしら" ], "comment": "hoopoe (species of Eurasian bird, Upupa epops)" },
		{ "question": "扁桃", "answers": [ "アーモンド" ], "comment": "sweet almond (Prunus dulcis)\ntonsil" },
		{ "question": "手巾", "answers": [ "ハンカチ" ], "comment": "(hand) towel\nhandkerchief" },
		{ "question": "手風琴", "answers": [ "アコーディオン" ], "comment": "accordion; melodeon; concertina" },
		{ "question": "把手", "answers": [ "ハンドル" ], "comment": "handle; grip; knob" },
		{ "question": "抽斗", "answers": [ "ひきだし" ], "comment": "drawer\nwithdrawal; drawing out\nvariety of knowledge and experience useful for handling things impromptu" },
		{ "question": "拳螺", "answers": [ "さざえ" ], "comment": "turban shell (any mollusc of the family Turbinidae, esp. the horned turban, Turbo cornutus)" },
		{ "question": "掃桑波敦", "answers": [ "サウサンプトン" ]},
		{ "question": "掏児", "answers": [ "すり" ], "comment": "pickpocket" },
		{ "question": "掏摸", "answers": [ "すり" ], "comment": "pickpocket" },
		{ "question": "排球", "answers": [ "バレーボール" ], "comment": "volleyball" },
		{ "question": "提琴", "answers": [ "バイオリン" ], "comment": "tiqin (2 or 4-stringed Chinese instrument played with a bow)\nviolin" },
		{ "question": "揚羽蝶", "answers": [ "あげはちょう" ], "comment": "swallowtail butterfly (esp. the citrus swallowtail butterfly, Papilio xuthus)" },
		{ "question": "摩洛哥", "answers": [ "モロッコ" ], "comment": "Morocco" },
		{ "question": "摩西", "answers": [ "モーセ" ]},
		{ "question": "撒哈拉", "answers": [ "サハラ" ]},
		{ "question": "撞球", "answers": [ "ビリヤード" ], "comment": "billiards" },
		{ "question": "撥条", "answers": [ "ばね" ], "comment": "spring (e.g. coil, leaf); mainspring; power spring" },
		{ "question": "撫子", "answers": [ "なでしこ" ], "comment": "pink (any flower of genus Dianthus, esp. the fringed pink, Dianthus superbus)\nlovable, caressable girl" },
		{ "question": "改羅", "answers": [ "カイロ" ]},
		{ "question": "敦盛草", "answers": [ "あつもりそう" ], "comment": "large-flowered cypripedium (species of lady's slipper, Cypripedium macranthos, esp. Cypripedium macranthos var. speciosum)" },
		{ "question": "文蛤", "answers": [ "はまぐり" ], "comment": "common orient clam (Meretrix lusoria)" },
		{ "question": "斑", "answers": [ "まだら" ], "comment": "uneven; irregular; speckled; mottled\nerratic; inconsistent\nfickle; capricious; fitful\nspots; speckles; mottles\nspots; speckles; mottles\nspeckled; spotted" },
		{ "question": "斑猫", "answers": [ "はんみょう" ], "comment": "tiger beetle (esp. the Japanese tiger beetle, Cicindela japonica)\nblister beetle; oil beetle" },
		{ "question": "斑馬", "answers": [ "しまうま" ], "comment": "zebra\nspeckled horse" },
		{ "question": "斯達林", "answers": [ "スターリン" ]},
		{ "question": "新嘉坡", "answers": [ "シンガポール" ], "comment": "Singapore" },
		{ "question": "新英土", "answers": [ "ニューイングランド" ]},
		{ "question": "新西蘭", "answers": [ "ニュージーランド" ], "comment": "New Zealand" },
		{ "question": "於麟飛", "answers": [ "オリンピア" ]},
		{ "question": "日暮らし", "answers": [ "ひぐらし" ], "comment": "from morning to evening; all day long" },
		{ "question": "日計", "answers": [ "ひばかり" ], "comment": "daily account; daily expenses\nAsian keelback (Amphiesma vibakari)" },
		{ "question": "易卜生", "answers": [ "イプセン" ]},
		{ "question": "映日果", "answers": [ "いちじく" ], "comment": "common fig (Ficus carica); fig; fig tree" },
		{ "question": "春菊", "answers": [ "しゅんぎく" ], "comment": "edible chrysanthemum (Chrysanthemum coronarium); crown daisy; garland chrysanthemum" },
		{ "question": "時化", "answers": [ "しけ" ], "comment": "stormy weather (at sea)\npoor catch of fish (due to stormy seas)\npoor turn-out; recession" },
		{ "question": "時鳥", "answers": [ "ほととぎす" ], "comment": "lesser cuckoo (Cuculus poliocephalus)" },
		{ "question": "晩克坡", "answers": [ "バンクーバー" ]},
		{ "question": "普魯西", "answers": [ "プロシア" ], "comment": "Prussia" },
		{ "question": "智利", "answers": [ "チリ" ], "comment": "Chile" },
		{ "question": "暖簾", "answers": [ "のれん" ], "comment": "(short) sign curtain hung at shop entrance\nreputation (of a store); goodwill" },
		{ "question": "更紗", "answers": [ "サラサ" ], "comment": "cotton print; calico" },
		{ "question": "曹達", "answers": [ "ソーダ" ], "comment": "soda" },
		{ "question": "曼澈斯特", "answers": [ "マンチェスター" ]},
		{ "question": "木乃伊", "answers": [ "みいら" ], "comment": "mummy" },
		{ "question": "木履", "answers": [ "ぽっくり" ], "comment": "girl's lacquered wooden geta\nwooden footwear; clogs; sabots" },
		{ "question": "木栓", "answers": [ "コルク" ], "comment": "wooden plug; cork; tampion" },
		{ "question": "木犀", "answers": [ "もくせい" ], "comment": "fragrant olive; sweet olive; Osmanthus fragrans; Olea fragrans" },
		{ "question": "木瓜", "answers": [ "ぼけ" ], "comment": "Japanese quince (Chaenomeles speciosa); flowering quince\nfamily crest based on a japonica flower\nstyle of joruri narrative used for kabuki dances" },
		{ "question": "木目", "answers": [ "きめ" ], "comment": "texture (e.g. skin, fabric)\ngrain (e.g. wood)\ndetail\ngrain (of wood); curly grain" },
		{ "question": "木菟", "answers": [ "みみずく" ], "comment": "horned owl" },
		{ "question": "木賊", "answers": [ "とくさ" ], "comment": "scouring rushes; Equisetum hyemale; common horsetail" },
		{ "question": "木通", "answers": [ "あけび" ], "comment": "chocolate-vine (Akebia quinata); fiveleaf; fiveleaf akebia\nfruit of the akebia" },
		{ "question": "朱欒", "answers": [ "ザボン" ], "comment": "shaddock; pomelo; Citrus maximus; Citrus grandis; Citrus decumana" },
		{ "question": "朱鷺", "answers": [ "とき" ], "comment": "Japanese crested ibis (Nipponia nippon); crested ibis" },
		{ "question": "杏", "answers": [ "あんず" ], "comment": "apricot (Prunus armeniaca)" },
		{ "question": "杏子", "answers": [ "あんず" ], "comment": "apricot (Prunus armeniaca)" },
		{ "question": "杓文字", "answers": [ "しゃもじ" ], "comment": "wooden spoon; ladle; rice scoop" },
		{ "question": "杜父魚", "answers": [ "かじか" ], "comment": "sculpin (any fish of family Cottidae, incl. the bullheads and the miller's-thumb)\nJapanese fluvial sculpin (Cottus pollux)\nfourspine sculpin (species of fish, Cottus kazika)" },
		{ "question": "杜若", "answers": [ "かきつばた" ], "comment": "rabbitear iris (Iris laevigata)" },
		{ "question": "杜鵑", "answers": [ "ほととぎす" ], "comment": "lesser cuckoo (Cuculus poliocephalus)" },
		{ "question": "束子", "answers": [ "たわし" ], "comment": "scrubbing brush; scourer" },
		{ "question": "条虫", "answers": [ "さなだむし" ], "comment": "cestode; tapeworm" },
		{ "question": "杼", "answers": [ "とち" ], "comment": "Japanese horse chestnut (Aesculus turbinata)\n10^24\nshuttle (of a loom)" },
		{ "question": "松魚", "answers": [ "かつお" ], "comment": "skipjack tuna (Katsuwonus pelamis); oceanic bonito; victorfish" },
		{ "question": "枇杷", "answers": [ "びわ" ], "comment": "loquat (Eriobotrya japonica); Japanese medlar" },
		{ "question": "林檎", "answers": [ "りんご" ], "comment": "apple (fruit)\napple tree (Malus pumila)" },
		{ "question": "林肯", "answers": [ "リンカーン" ]},
		{ "question": "枹", "answers": [ "なら" ], "comment": "plectrum; pick\ndrumstick for Japanese drums (e.g. taiko)\noak (esp. Quercus serrata)" },
		{ "question": "柊", "answers": [ "ひいらぎ" ], "comment": "holly olive (Osmanthus heterophyllus); false holly\nholly\nspotnape ponyfish (Leiognathus nuchalis)" },
		{ "question": "柘植", "answers": [ "つげ" ], "comment": "Japanese box tree (Buxus microphylla var. japonica); Japanese boxwood" },
		{ "question": "柘榴", "answers": [ "ざくろ" ], "comment": "pomegranate (Punica granatum)" },
		{ "question": "柚", "answers": [ "ゆず" ], "comment": "yuzu (Citrus ichangensis x C. reticulata)" },
		{ "question": "柚子", "answers": [ "ゆず" ], "comment": "yuzu (Citrus ichangensis x C. reticulata)" },
		{ "question": "柞", "answers": [ "なら" ], "comment": "oak (esp. Quercus serrata)\nDistylium racemosum (evergreen tree of the winter-hazel genus)" },
		{ "question": "柳葉魚", "answers": [ "ししゃも" ], "comment": "shishamo smelt (Spirinchus lanceolatus)" },
		{ "question": "栂", "answers": [ "つが" ], "comment": "southern Japanese hemlock (species of conifer native to Japan, Tsuga sieboldii)" },
		{ "question": "栃", "answers": [ "とち" ], "comment": "Japanese horse chestnut (Aesculus turbinata)" },
		{ "question": "栄螺", "answers": [ "さざえ" ], "comment": "turban shell (any mollusc of the family Turbinidae, esp. the horned turban, Turbo cornutus)" },
		{ "question": "栗鼠", "answers": [ "りす" ], "comment": "squirrel (excluding flying squirrels)\nJapanese squirrel (Sciurus lis)" },
		{ "question": "格勒格力", "answers": [ "グレゴリー" ]},
		{ "question": "格林威治", "answers": [ "グリニッジ" ]},
		{ "question": "桃花鳥", "answers": [ "とき" ], "comment": "Japanese crested ibis (Nipponia nippon); crested ibis" },
		{ "question": "桑港", "answers": [ "サンフランシスコ" ]},
		{ "question": "桔梗", "answers": [ "ききょう" ], "comment": "Chinese bellflower; Platycodon grandiflorum" },
		{ "question": "桜府", "answers": [ "サクラメント" ]},
		{ "question": "桧", "answers": [ "ひのき" ], "comment": "hinoki cypress (Chamaecyparis obtusa); Japanese cypress" },
		{ "question": "梃", "answers": [ "てこ" ], "comment": "counter for long and narrow things such as guns, scissors, spades, hoes, inksticks, palanquins, candles, jinrikishas, shamisen, oars, etc.\nlever" },
		{ "question": "梃子", "answers": [ "てこ" ], "comment": "lever" },
		{ "question": "梅特林克", "answers": [ "メーテルリンク" ]},
		{ "question": "梔子", "answers": [ "くちなし" ], "comment": "Cape jasmine (Gardenia jasminoides); Cape jessamine; gardenia" },
		{ "question": "梟", "answers": [ "ふくろう" ], "comment": "owl (esp. the Ural owl, Strix uralensis)" },
		{ "question": "梭子魚", "answers": [ "かます" ], "comment": "barracuda" },
		{ "question": "梭尾螺", "answers": [ "ほらがい" ], "comment": "conch (esp. Charonia tritonis); trumpet shell" },
		{ "question": "梭魚", "answers": [ "かます" ], "comment": "barracuda" },
		{ "question": "梯", "answers": [ "はしご" ], "comment": "ladder\nstairs\ngoing to several places in succession (e.g. barhopping)\nsuspension bridge; viaduct; temporary bridge\nmediation; go-between\nladder" },
		{ "question": "梯子", "answers": [ "はしご" ], "comment": "ladder\nstairs\ngoing to several places in succession (e.g. barhopping)" },
		{ "question": "棒振", "answers": [ "ぼうふら" ], "comment": "mosquito larva; wriggler; maggot" },
		{ "question": "棕梠", "answers": [ "しゅろ" ], "comment": "Chinese windmill palm (Trachycarpus fortunei); Chusan palm; hemp palm" },
		{ "question": "棕櫚", "answers": [ "しゅろ" ], "comment": "Chinese windmill palm (Trachycarpus fortunei); Chusan palm; hemp palm" },
		{ "question": "椋鳥", "answers": [ "むくどり" ], "comment": "grey starling (Sturnus cineraceus); gray starling; white-cheeked starling\nstarling (any bird of family Sturnidae)\nbumpkin; gullible person\nsixty-nine (sexual position)" },
		{ "question": "椎", "answers": [ "つち" ], "comment": "any beech tree of genus Castanopsis; chinquapin; chinkapin" },
		{ "question": "椎茸", "answers": [ "しいたけ" ], "comment": "shiitake mushroom (Lentinula edodes)" },
		{ "question": "椚", "answers": [ "くぬぎ" ], "comment": "sawtooth oak (Quercus acutissima)" },
		{ "question": "椰子", "answers": [ "やし" ], "comment": "palm tree" },
		{ "question": "椿象", "answers": [ "かめむし" ], "comment": "shield bug; stink bug" },
		{ "question": "楓", "answers": [ "かえで" ], "comment": "maple (tree) (Acer spp.)\nFormosan sweetgum (Liquidambar formosana)" },
		{ "question": "楠", "answers": [ "くすのき" ], "comment": "camphor tree (Cinnamomum camphora); camphorwood; camphor laurel" },
		{ "question": "楡", "answers": [ "にれ" ], "comment": "elm tree (esp. the Japanese elm, Ulmus davidiana var. japonica)" },
		{ "question": "楢", "answers": [ "なら" ], "comment": "oak (esp. Quercus serrata)" },
		{ "question": "業平", "answers": [ "ジャパン" ]},
		{ "question": "極光", "answers": [ "オーロラ" ], "comment": "northern or southern lights; aurora borealis or australis" },
		{ "question": "榎", "answers": [ "えのき" ], "comment": "Japanese hackberry (Celtis sinensis var. japonica); Chinese nettle tree\nenoki mushroom (Flammulina velutipes); winter mushroom; velvet shank; enokitake; enokidake" },
		{ "question": "槌", "answers": [ "つち" ], "comment": "hammer; mallet; sledge(hammer); gavel" },
		{ "question": "槻", "answers": [ "けやき" ], "comment": "Japanese zelkova (species of elm-like tree, Zelkowa serrata)" },
		{ "question": "樅", "answers": [ "もみ" ], "comment": "fir tree" },
		{ "question": "樟", "answers": [ "くすのき" ], "comment": "camphor tree (Cinnamomum camphora); camphorwood; camphor laurel" },
		{ "question": "樫", "answers": [ "かし" ], "comment": "evergreen oak" },
		{ "question": "樹懶", "answers": [ "なまけもの" ], "comment": "sloth (Sth. Am. tree-dwelling mammal)" },
		{ "question": "橄欖", "answers": [ "オリーブ" ], "comment": "Chinese white olive (Canarium album)\nolive (Olea europea)" },
		{ "question": "橙", "answers": [ "だいだい" ], "comment": "bitter orange (Citrus aurantium)" },
		{ "question": "橡", "answers": [ "くぬぎ","とち" ], "comment": "acorn\nJapanese horse chestnut (Aesculus turbinata)\nsawtooth oak (Quercus acutissima)\nsawtooth oak (Quercus acutissima); acorn\ndark grey; dark gray" },
		{ "question": "橿", "answers": [ "かし" ], "comment": "evergreen oak" },
		{ "question": "檜", "answers": [ "ひのき" ], "comment": "hinoki cypress (Chamaecyparis obtusa); Japanese cypress" },
		{ "question": "檬果", "answers": [ "マンゴー" ]},
		{ "question": "檸檬", "answers": [ "レモン" ], "comment": "lemon" },
		{ "question": "櫟", "answers": [ "くぬぎ" ], "comment": "sawtooth oak (Quercus acutissima)\nQuercus gilva (species of oak)" },
		{ "question": "櫨", "answers": [ "はぜのき" ], "comment": "wax tree (Toxicodendron succedaneum); Japanese wax tree" },
		{ "question": "櫪", "answers": [ "くぬぎ" ], "comment": "sawtooth oak (Quercus acutissima)" },
		{ "question": "欅", "answers": [ "けやき" ], "comment": "Japanese zelkova (species of elm-like tree, Zelkowa serrata)" },
		{ "question": "欠伸", "answers": [ "あくび" ], "comment": "yawn; yawning" },
		{ "question": "欧羅巴", "answers": [ "ヨーロッパ" ], "comment": "Europe" },
		{ "question": "款冬", "answers": [ "ふき" ], "comment": "giant butterbur (Petasites japonicus); Japanese sweet coltsfoot\nkerria (Kerria japonica); Japanese yellow rose\nbright golden yellow\ngold coin\ngiant butterbur\nJapanese silverleaf (Farfugium japonicum)" },
		{ "question": "歌留多", "answers": [ "カルタ" ], "comment": "karuta; traditional Japanese playing cards" },
		{ "question": "歌白尼", "answers": [ "コペルニクス" ]},
		{ "question": "歩行虫", "answers": [ "おさむし","ごみむし" ], "comment": "ground beetle; carabid (esp. of subfamily Carabinae)\nmillipede\nground beetle; carabid (esp. of superfamily Caraboidea, but excluding subfamily Carabinae)\nAnisodactylus signatus (species of ground beetle)" },
		{ "question": "歯朶", "answers": [ "しだ" ], "comment": "fern (esp. species Gleichenia japonica); fernery" },
		{ "question": "比律賓", "answers": [ "フィリピン" ], "comment": "Philippines" },
		{ "question": "比目魚", "answers": [ "ひらめ" ], "comment": "flounder (esp. the large-tooth flounders of family Paralichthyidae, but also lefteye flounders of family Bothidae)\nbastard halibut; olive flounder (Paralichthys olivaceus)" },
		{ "question": "氈鹿", "answers": [ "かもしか" ], "comment": "serow; wild goat" },
		{ "question": "水松食貝", "answers": [ "みるくいがい" ], "comment": "mirugai clam (Tresus keenae, species of gaper clam)" },
		{ "question": "水母", "answers": [ "くらげ" ], "comment": "jellyfish\nmedusa" },
		{ "question": "水澄", "answers": [ "みずすまし" ], "comment": "whirligig beetle (any insect of family Gyrinidae, esp. the Japanese whirligig beetle, Gyrinus japonicus)\npond skater; water strider" },
		{ "question": "水爬虫", "answers": [ "たがめ" ], "comment": "Lethocerus deyrollei (species of giant water bug)" },
		{ "question": "水瓜", "answers": [ "すいか" ], "comment": "watermelon (Citrullus lanatus)" },
		{ "question": "水薙鳥", "answers": [ "みずなぎどり" ], "comment": "petrel (esp. petrels of family Procellariidae)" },
		{ "question": "水蚤", "answers": [ "みじんこ" ]},
		{ "question": "水蜻蛉", "answers": [ "みずとんぼ" ], "comment": "Habenaria sagittifera (species of bog orchid)" },
		{ "question": "水蟷螂", "answers": [ "みずかまきり" ], "comment": "water stick; water scorpion" },
		{ "question": "水雲", "answers": [ "もずく" ], "comment": "mozuku (Cladosiphon okamuranus and Sphaerotrichia divaricata, types of edible seaweed)" },
		{ "question": "水馬", "answers": [ "あめんぼ" ], "comment": "pond skater (any insect of family Gerridae); water strider\ncrossing water with a horse" },
		{ "question": "水鶏", "answers": [ "くいな" ], "comment": "rail (any bird of family Rallidae, esp. the water rail, Rallus aquaticus)" },
		{ "question": "水黽", "answers": [ "あめんぼ" ], "comment": "pond skater (any insect of family Gerridae); water strider" },
		{ "question": "氷菓子", "answers": [ "アイスクリーム" ], "comment": "frozen dessert" },
		{ "question": "汗疹", "answers": [ "あせも" ], "comment": "prickly heat; heat rash; miliaria" },
		{ "question": "汽艇", "answers": [ "ランチ" ], "comment": "(steam) launch" },
		{ "question": "沙翁", "answers": [ "シェークスピア" ]},
		{ "question": "沙蚕", "answers": [ "ごかい" ], "comment": "ragworm; sandworm; clam worm (Hediste)" },
		{ "question": "沙魚", "answers": [ "はぜ" ], "comment": "goby (fish)\nyellowfin goby (Acanthogobius flavimanus)" },
		{ "question": "河豚", "answers": [ "ふぐ" ], "comment": "puffer fish; blow fish; fugu; globefish; swellfish" },
		{ "question": "河貝子", "answers": [ "かわにな" ]},
		{ "question": "河馬", "answers": [ "かば" ], "comment": "hippopotamus (Hippopotamus amphibius)" },
		{ "question": "法螺貝", "answers": [ "ほらがい" ], "comment": "conch (esp. Charonia tritonis); trumpet shell" },
		{ "question": "波布", "answers": [ "はぶ" ], "comment": "habu (Trimeresurus flavoviridis); yellow-spotted pit viper" },
		{ "question": "波斯", "answers": [ "ペルシャ" ], "comment": "Persia" },
		{ "question": "波蘭", "answers": [ "ポーランド" ], "comment": "Poland" },
		{ "question": "泥婆羅", "answers": [ "ネパール" ]},
		{ "question": "泥障", "answers": [ "あおり" ], "comment": "saddle flap" },
		{ "question": "泥鰌", "answers": [ "どじょう" ], "comment": "loach (any fish of family Cobitidae)\nweather loach (Misgurnus anguillicaudatus)" },
		{ "question": "泰", "answers": [ "タイ" ], "comment": "Thailand" },
		{ "question": "洋傘", "answers": [ "パラソル" ], "comment": "(Western-style) umbrella; parasol" },
		{ "question": "洋灯", "answers": [ "ランプ" ], "comment": "lamp" },
		{ "question": "洋琴", "answers": [ "ピアノ" ], "comment": "yangqin (Chinese hammered dulcimer)\npiano" },
		{ "question": "洋袴", "answers": [ "ズボン" ]},
		{ "question": "洋銀", "answers": [ "ニッケル" ], "comment": "German silver; nickel silver\nsilver coinage imported to Japan during the late Edo and early Meiji periods" },
		{ "question": "洗熊", "answers": [ "あらいぐま" ], "comment": "common raccoon (Procyon lotor)" },
		{ "question": "洪牙利", "answers": [ "ハンガリー" ], "comment": "Hungary" },
		{ "question": "浅葱", "answers": [ "あさつき" ], "comment": "pale blue-green\nchive (edible plant, Allium schoenoprasum)" },
		{ "question": "浅蜊", "answers": [ "あさり" ], "comment": "Manila clam (Ruditapes philippinarum)" },
		{ "question": "浜木綿", "answers": [ "はまゆう" ], "comment": "crinum" },
		{ "question": "浣熊", "answers": [ "あらいぐま" ], "comment": "common raccoon (Procyon lotor)" },
		{ "question": "浪漫", "answers": [ "ロマン" ], "comment": "romance (e.g. Arthurian romances)\nnovel\nromance; love affair\nadventurous spirit; impossible dream; great ambition" },
		{ "question": "浮塵子", "answers": [ "うんか" ], "comment": "plant hopper (any insect of family Delphacidae); leafhopper" },
		{ "question": "海星", "answers": [ "ひとで" ], "comment": "starfish; sea star; asteroid; any echinoderm of the class Asteroidea\nnorthern Pacific seastar (Asterias amurensis)" },
		{ "question": "海月", "answers": [ "くらげ" ], "comment": "jellyfish\nmedusa" },
		{ "question": "海松食貝", "answers": [ "みるくいがい" ], "comment": "mirugai clam (Tresus keenae, species of gaper clam)" },
		{ "question": "海栗", "answers": [ "うに" ], "comment": "sea urchin\nseasoned sea urchin eggs" },
		{ "question": "海牛", "answers": [ "うみうし" ], "comment": "sirenian (any aquatic mammal of order Sirenia, incl. manatees, and dugongs); sea cow\nsea slug (various orthogastropod species, esp. of order Nudibranchia); nudibranch" },
		{ "question": "海獺", "answers": [ "ラッコ" ], "comment": "sea otter (Enhydra lutris)\nsea lion" },
		{ "question": "海盤車", "answers": [ "ひとで" ], "comment": "starfish; sea star; asteroid; any echinoderm of the class Asteroidea\nnorthern Pacific seastar (Asterias amurensis)" },
		{ "question": "海老", "answers": [ "えび" ], "comment": "prawn; shrimp; lobster; crayfish" },
		{ "question": "海老根", "answers": [ "えびね" ], "comment": "Calanthe discolor (species of orchid)" },
		{ "question": "海胆", "answers": [ "うに" ], "comment": "sea urchin\nseasoned sea urchin eggs" },
		{ "question": "海蘊", "answers": [ "もずく" ], "comment": "mozuku (Cladosiphon okamuranus and Sphaerotrichia divaricata, types of edible seaweed)" },
		{ "question": "海蛍", "answers": [ "うみほたる" ], "comment": "sea firefly (Vargula hilgendorfii); seed shrimp" },
		{ "question": "海豚", "answers": [ "いるか" ], "comment": "dolphin (or other small toothed whales, such as porpoises, belugas, etc.)" },
		{ "question": "海象", "answers": [ "セイウチ" ], "comment": "walrus (Odobenus rosmarus)\nelephant seal (Mirounga spp.)\nmarine phenomenon" },
		{ "question": "海豹", "answers": [ "あざらし" ], "comment": "true seal (animal); earless seal" },
		{ "question": "海鞘", "answers": [ "ほや" ], "comment": "sea squirt; ascidian" },
		{ "question": "海馬", "answers": [ "セイウチ","とど" ], "comment": "walrus (Odobenus rosmarus)\nelephant seal (Mirounga spp.)\nSteller's sea lion; Northern sea lion\neared seal (esp. the California sea lion, Zalophus californianus); sea lion\nseahorse; sea horse\nhippocampus\nwalrus" },
		{ "question": "海驢", "answers": [ "あしか" ], "comment": "eared seal (esp. the California sea lion, Zalophus californianus); sea lion" },
		{ "question": "海鷂魚", "answers": [ "えい" ], "comment": "ray (fish); stingray" },
		{ "question": "海鼠", "answers": [ "なまこ" ], "comment": "sea cucumber (Holothuroidea spp.)" },
		{ "question": "涎", "answers": [ "よだれ" ], "comment": "drool" },
		{ "question": "混凝土", "answers": [ "コンクリート" ], "comment": "concrete" },
		{ "question": "混合酒", "answers": [ "カクテル" ], "comment": "cocktail; mixed drink; blended liquor" },
		{ "question": "温突", "answers": [ "オンドル" ], "comment": "Korean floor heater" },
		{ "question": "満天星", "answers": [ "どうだんつつじ" ], "comment": "Enkianthus perulatus (species of flowering plant in the Ericaceae family)" },
		{ "question": "源五郎", "answers": [ "げんごろう" ], "comment": "diving beetle\nJapanese predacious diving beetle (Cybister japonicus)" },
		{ "question": "滴", "answers": [ "しずく" ], "comment": "drop (of water); drip\ndripping; drop\ncounter for drops of liquid" },
		{ "question": "漢堡", "answers": [ "ハンブルク" ]},
		{ "question": "澱粉", "answers": [ "でんぷん" ], "comment": "starch" },
		{ "question": "澳門", "answers": [ "マカオ" ], "comment": "Macau; Macao" },
		{ "question": "濠太剌利", "answers": [ "オーストラリア" ], "comment": "Australia" },
		{ "question": "火燵", "answers": [ "こたつ" ], "comment": "kotatsu; table over an electric heater (orig. a charcoal brazier in a floor well) with a hanging quilt that retains heat" },
		{ "question": "火酒", "answers": [ "ウイスキー" ], "comment": "strong drink" },
		{ "question": "火食鳥", "answers": [ "ひくいどり" ], "comment": "cassowary (Casuarius spp.)" },
		{ "question": "灰殻", "answers": [ "ハイカラ" ], "comment": "ashes" },
		{ "question": "灰汁", "answers": [ "あく" ], "comment": "lye\nharsh taste; astringency\nscum (formed when cooking some foods)\n(excessive) strength of will" },
		{ "question": "炬燵", "answers": [ "こたつ" ], "comment": "kotatsu; table over an electric heater (orig. a charcoal brazier in a floor well) with a hanging quilt that retains heat" },
		{ "question": "為体", "answers": [ "ていたらく" ], "comment": "state of affairs; predicament" },
		{ "question": "烏", "answers": [ "からす" ], "comment": "crow (Corvus spp.); raven" },
		{ "question": "烏克蘭", "answers": [ "ウクライナ" ], "comment": "Ukraine" },
		{ "question": "烏賊", "answers": [ "いか" ], "comment": "cuttlefish; squid" },
		{ "question": "烽火", "answers": [ "のろし" ], "comment": "beacon; skyrocket; signal fire; smoke signals\nstarting shot; starting signal" },
		{ "question": "無花果", "answers": [ "いちじく" ], "comment": "common fig (Ficus carica); fig; fig tree" },
		{ "question": "煎餅", "answers": [ "せんべい" ], "comment": "rice cracker; Japanese cracker; rice cookie; wafer" },
		{ "question": "煙管", "answers": [ "キセル" ], "comment": "kiseru; Japanese smoking pipe\nfire tube (of a fire-tube boiler)\nchimney\n(tobacco) pipe with metal tipped stem\nstolen train ride (only paying a local fare each end)" },
		{ "question": "煙草", "answers": [ "たばこ" ], "comment": "tobacco; cigarette; cigaret; cigar\ntobacco plant (Nicotiana tabacum)" },
		{ "question": "燐寸", "answers": [ "マッチ" ], "comment": "match (to light fire with)" },
		{ "question": "燕", "answers": [ "つばめ" ], "comment": "swallow (bird of the Hirundinidae family); martin\nbarn swallow (Hirundo rustica)\nyounger man involved with an older woman" },
		{ "question": "燭魚", "answers": [ "はたはた" ], "comment": "sailfin sandfish (Arctoscopus japonicus); Japanese sandfish" },
		{ "question": "爪哇", "answers": [ "ジャワ" ]},
		{ "question": "爪楊枝", "answers": [ "つまようじ" ], "comment": "toothpick" },
		{ "question": "牙買加", "answers": [ "ジャマイカ" ], "comment": "Jamaica" },
		{ "question": "牛尾魚", "answers": [ "こち" ], "comment": "flathead (esp. the bartailed flathead, Platycephalus indicus)" },
		{ "question": "牛津", "answers": [ "オックスフォード" ]},
		{ "question": "牛蒡", "answers": [ "ごぼう" ], "comment": "great burdock (Arctium lappa)" },
		{ "question": "牛酪", "answers": [ "バター" ], "comment": "butter" },
		{ "question": "牡蠣", "answers": [ "かき" ], "comment": "oyster; oyster shell" },
		{ "question": "犀", "answers": [ "さい" ], "comment": "rhinoceros" },
		{ "question": "犂", "answers": [ "すき" ], "comment": "spade\nplough; plow\nplow (esp. horse or ox-drawn); plough" },
		{ "question": "犬榧", "answers": [ "いぬがや" ], "comment": "Japanese plum-yew (Cephalotaxus harringtonia); Harrington's cephalotaxus; cowtail pine" },
		{ "question": "狐", "answers": [ "きつね" ], "comment": "fox (esp. the red fox, Vulpes vulpes)\nfox (i.e. a sly person)\nsoba or udon topped with deep-fried tofu\nlight brown" },
		{ "question": "狗母魚", "answers": [ "えそ" ], "comment": "lizardfish (any fish of family Synodontidae)" },
		{ "question": "独活", "answers": [ "うど" ], "comment": "udo (plant related to ginseng, used in medicine and cooking) (Aralia cordata)" },
		{ "question": "独逸", "answers": [ "ドイツ" ], "comment": "Germany" },
		{ "question": "狼", "answers": [ "おおかみ" ], "comment": "wolf (Canis lupus)\nwolf in sheep's clothing; womanizer" },
		{ "question": "狼煙", "answers": [ "のろし" ], "comment": "beacon; skyrocket; signal fire; smoke signals\nstarting shot; starting signal" },
		{ "question": "猟虎", "answers": [ "ラッコ" ], "comment": "sea otter (Enhydra lutris)" },
		{ "question": "猩猩蠅", "answers": [ "しょうじょうばえ" ], "comment": "fruit fly (any insect of family Drosophilidae); vinegar fly; pomace fly; banana fly" },
		{ "question": "猪", "answers": [ "いのしし" ], "comment": "wild boar\nbeast (esp. one used for its meat, such as a boar or a deer)\nhunting (of animals such as boar, deer, etc.)\nhog (esp. a wild boar, but also including the domesticated pig)" },
		{ "question": "獅子利", "answers": [ "シシリー" ]},
		{ "question": "獏", "answers": [ "ばく" ], "comment": "tapir (Tapirus spp.)\nmo; mythological Chinese chimera similar to a tapir, said to devour bad dreams" },
		{ "question": "獺", "answers": [ "かわうそ" ], "comment": "otter (Lutra lutra)\nJapanese river otter (Lutra lutra whiteleyi)" },
		{ "question": "獺虎", "answers": [ "ラッコ" ], "comment": "sea otter (Enhydra lutris)" },
		{ "question": "玄人", "answers": [ "くろうと" ], "comment": "expert; professional; master\nwoman in the nightlife business; demimondaine; geisha and prostitutes" },
		{ "question": "玉虫", "answers": [ "たまむし" ], "comment": "jewel beetle; Chrysochroa fulgidissima; insect with iridescent wings" },
		{ "question": "玉蜀黍", "answers": [ "とうもろこし" ], "comment": "corn (Zea mays); maize" },
		{ "question": "玖馬", "answers": [ "キューバ" ], "comment": "Cuba" },
		{ "question": "玳瑁", "answers": [ "たいまい" ], "comment": "hawksbill turtle (Eretmochelys imbricata)" },
		{ "question": "珈琲", "answers": [ "コーヒー" ], "comment": "coffee" },
		{ "question": "珊瑚", "answers": [ "さんご" ], "comment": "coral" },
		{ "question": "珠鶏", "answers": [ "ほろほろちょう" ], "comment": "helmeted guinea fowl (Numida meleagris)" },
		{ "question": "琴鳥", "answers": [ "ことどり" ], "comment": "superb lyrebird (Menura novaehollandiae)" },
		{ "question": "瑞典", "answers": [ "スウェーデン" ], "comment": "Sweden" },
		{ "question": "瑞西", "answers": [ "スイス" ], "comment": "Switzerland" },
		{ "question": "瓊脂", "answers": [ "ところてん" ]},
		{ "question": "瓜姆", "answers": [ "グアム" ]},
		{ "question": "瓢虫", "answers": [ "てんとうむし" ], "comment": "ladybug (Harmonia axyridis); ladybird" },
		{ "question": "瓦斯", "answers": [ "ガス" ], "comment": "gas (state of matter, e.g. poison gas, natural gas)\ngasoline; gas; petrol\ndense fog; thick fog\ngas stove; gas cooker; gas range\nflatulence; gas; wind; fart" },
		{ "question": "瓦格納", "answers": [ "ワグナー" ]},
		{ "question": "瓦的", "answers": [ "ワット" ]},
		{ "question": "甘蕉", "answers": [ "バナナ" ]},
		{ "question": "甘藍", "answers": [ "かんらん","キャベツ" ], "comment": "cabbage" },
		{ "question": "甘藷", "answers": [ "さつまいも" ], "comment": "sweet potato (Ipomoea batatas)" },
		{ "question": "生姜", "answers": [ "しょうが" ], "comment": "ginger (Zingiber officinale)\ndried ginger root (trad. medicine)" },
		{ "question": "生薑", "answers": [ "しょうが" ], "comment": "ginger (Zingiber officinale)\ndried ginger root (trad. medicine)" },
		{ "question": "田螺", "answers": [ "たにし" ], "comment": "pond snail (Viviparidae spp.)" },
		{ "question": "田鼈", "answers": [ "たがめ" ], "comment": "Lethocerus deyrollei (species of giant water bug)" },
		{ "question": "甲虫", "answers": [ "かぶとむし" ], "comment": "rhinoceros beetle (esp. the Japanese rhinoceros beetle, Trypoxylus dichotomus)\nbeetle" },
		{ "question": "甲谷佗", "answers": [ "カルカッタ" ]},
		{ "question": "疣", "answers": [ "いぼ" ], "comment": "wart" },
		{ "question": "痂", "answers": [ "かさぶた" ], "comment": "crust; scab" },
		{ "question": "痣", "answers": [ "あざ" ], "comment": "birthmark; nevus\nbruise" },
		{ "question": "瘡蓋", "answers": [ "かさぶた" ], "comment": "crust; scab" },
		{ "question": "瘤", "answers": [ "こぶ" ], "comment": "bump; lump; protuberance; swelling" },
		{ "question": "癌", "answers": [ "がん" ], "comment": "cancer" },
		{ "question": "発条", "answers": [ "ばね" ], "comment": "spring (e.g. coil, leaf); mainspring; power spring" },
		{ "question": "白檀", "answers": [ "びゃくだん" ], "comment": "sandalwood" },
		{ "question": "白耳義", "answers": [ "ベルギー" ], "comment": "Belgium" },
		{ "question": "白蝋虫", "answers": [ "うんか" ], "comment": "plant hopper (any insect of family Delphacidae); leafhopper" },
		{ "question": "百合", "answers": [ "ゆり" ], "comment": "lily (Lilium spp.)\ncomics and novels about female homosexuality" },
		{ "question": "百日紅", "answers": [ "さるすべり" ], "comment": "crape myrtle (Lagerstroemia indica)" },
		{ "question": "百舌", "answers": [ "もず" ], "comment": "shrike (any bird of family Laniidae)\nbull-headed shrike (Lanius bucephalus); butcher bird" },
		{ "question": "百舌鳥", "answers": [ "もず" ], "comment": "shrike (any bird of family Laniidae)\nbull-headed shrike (Lanius bucephalus); butcher bird" },
		{ "question": "百足", "answers": [ "むかで" ], "comment": "centipede" },
		{ "question": "的鯛", "answers": [ "まとうだい" ], "comment": "John Dory (Zeus faber)" },
		{ "question": "皮剥", "answers": [ "かわはぎ" ], "comment": "thread-sail filefish (Stephanolepis cirrhifer)\nskinning (an animal); stripping (a tree of its bark); barking; skinner; barker" },
		{ "question": "皴", "answers": [ "しわ" ], "comment": "wrinkle; crease\nripple" },
		{ "question": "皺", "answers": [ "しわ" ], "comment": "wrinkle; crease\nripple\nbumpy texture of a material (esp. woven fabric)\ncreases in an eboshi hat" },
		{ "question": "目張", "answers": [ "めばる" ], "comment": "black rockfish (Sebastes inermis); darkbanded rockfish" },
		{ "question": "目眩", "answers": [ "めまい" ], "comment": "dizziness; giddiness; vertigo" },
		{ "question": "目高", "answers": [ "めだか" ], "comment": "Japanese rice fish (Oryzias latipes); killifish; Japanese medaka" },
		{ "question": "真田虫", "answers": [ "さなだむし" ], "comment": "tapeworm" },
		{ "question": "眩暈", "answers": [ "めまい" ], "comment": "dizziness; giddiness; vertigo" },
		{ "question": "眼張", "answers": [ "めばる" ], "comment": "black rockfish (Sebastes inermis); darkbanded rockfish" },
		{ "question": "睫", "answers": [ "まつげ" ], "comment": "eyelashes" },
		{ "question": "睫毛", "answers": [ "まつげ" ], "comment": "eyelashes" },
		{ "question": "瞿麦", "answers": [ "なでしこ" ], "comment": "pink (any flower of genus Dianthus, esp. the fringed pink, Dianthus superbus)\nlovable, caressable girl" },
		{ "question": "矛", "answers": [ "ほこ" ], "comment": "long-handled Chinese spear; lance; pike\nweapon; arms\ngrip of a bow" },
		{ "question": "短艇", "answers": [ "ボート" ], "comment": "(small) boat" },
		{ "question": "石伏魚", "answers": [ "ごり" ]},
		{ "question": "石南花", "answers": [ "しゃくなげ" ], "comment": "rhododendron" },
		{ "question": "石楠花", "answers": [ "しゃくなげ" ], "comment": "rhododendron" },
		{ "question": "石榴", "answers": [ "ざくろ" ], "comment": "pomegranate (Punica granatum)" },
		{ "question": "石決明", "answers": [ "あわび" ], "comment": "abalone; ear shell\npowdered abalone shell (used in Chinese medicine)" },
		{ "question": "石竜子", "answers": [ "とかげ" ], "comment": "lizard\nskink lizard (Scincidae spp.)" },
		{ "question": "石鹸", "answers": [ "せっけん","シャボン" ], "comment": "soap" },
		{ "question": "砥草", "answers": [ "とくさ" ], "comment": "scouring rushes; Equisetum hyemale; common horsetail" },
		{ "question": "碇", "answers": [ "いかり" ], "comment": "anchor" },
		{ "question": "磐谷", "answers": [ "バンコク" ]},
		{ "question": "磯巾着", "answers": [ "いそぎんちゃく" ], "comment": "sea anemone" },
		{ "question": "福特", "answers": [ "フォード" ]},
		{ "question": "秋刀魚", "answers": [ "さんま" ], "comment": "Pacific saury (Cololabis saira); mackerel pike" },
		{ "question": "秋桜", "answers": [ "コスモス" ], "comment": "cosmos (flower)" },
		{ "question": "秋沙", "answers": [ "あいさ" ], "comment": "merganser (any duck of genus Mergus)" },
		{ "question": "秋茜", "answers": [ "あきあかね" ], "comment": "var. of red dragonfly (Sympetrum frequens)" },
		{ "question": "秘露", "answers": [ "ペルー" ], "comment": "Peru" },
		{ "question": "秧鶏", "answers": [ "くいな" ], "comment": "rail (any bird of family Rallidae, esp. the water rail, Rallus aquaticus)" },
		{ "question": "稚海藻", "answers": [ "わかめ" ], "comment": "wakame (species of edible brown seaweed, Undaria pinnatifida)" },
		{ "question": "稲妻", "answers": [ "いなずま" ], "comment": "lightning; flash of lightning; lightning bolt" },
		{ "question": "稲子", "answers": [ "いなご" ], "comment": "rice grasshopper (of genus Oxya)\ngrasshopper; locust (of family Catantopidae)" },
		{ "question": "稷", "answers": [ "きび" ], "comment": "(common) millet (Panicum miliaceium); proso millet" },
		{ "question": "穀象虫", "answers": [ "こくぞうむし" ], "comment": "maize weevil (Sitophilus zeamais)" },
		{ "question": "穴子", "answers": [ "あなご" ], "comment": "garden eel; conger eel (esp. the common Japanese conger, Conger myriaster)" },
		{ "question": "穿山甲", "answers": [ "せんざんこう" ], "comment": "pangolin; scaly anteater; trenggiling" },
		{ "question": "突尼斯", "answers": [ "チュニジア" ], "comment": "Tunisia" },
		{ "question": "窒扶斯", "answers": [ "チフス" ], "comment": "typhoid fever; typhus" },
		{ "question": "竜胆", "answers": [ "りんどう" ], "comment": "gentian (Gentiana scabra var. buergeri); autumn bellflower" },
		{ "question": "竜蝨", "answers": [ "げんごろう" ]},
		{ "question": "章魚", "answers": [ "たこ" ], "comment": "octopus" },
		{ "question": "竹根蛇", "answers": [ "ひばかり" ], "comment": "Asian keelback (Amphiesma vibakari)" },
		{ "question": "竹節虫", "answers": [ "ななふし" ], "comment": "walking stick (any insect of order Phasmatodea); walkingstick; stick insect; leaf insect" },
		{ "question": "笄蛭", "answers": [ "こうがいびる" ]},
		{ "question": "笊", "answers": [ "ざる" ], "comment": "draining basket (traditionally made of bamboo); colander; strainer; sieve\nzaru soba (soba served on a bamboo draining basket with dipping sauce)\nstrong drinker; someone who can drink like a fish" },
		{ "question": "笋", "answers": [ "たけのこ" ], "comment": "bamboo shoot\ninexperienced doctor; quack" },
		{ "question": "笠子", "answers": [ "かさご" ], "comment": "scorpionfish\nmarbled rockfish (Sebastiscus marmoratus)" },
		{ "question": "筆頭菜", "answers": [ "つくし" ], "comment": "fertile shoot of field horsetail\nwooden stick with a burned tip (used to create underdrawings)" },
		{ "question": "筍", "answers": [ "たけのこ" ], "comment": "bamboo shoot\ninexperienced doctor; quack" },
		{ "question": "筬虫", "answers": [ "おさむし" ], "comment": "ground beetle; carabid (esp. of subfamily Carabinae)\nmillipede" },
		{ "question": "箆", "answers": [ "へら" ], "comment": "spatula\nshaft (of an arrow)\narrow bamboo (Pseudosasa japonica)" },
		{ "question": "箒", "answers": [ "ほうき" ], "comment": "broom" },
		{ "question": "箪笥", "answers": [ "たんす" ], "comment": "chest of drawers; bureau; cabinet; tansu; dresser" },
		{ "question": "篦鷺", "answers": [ "へらさぎ" ]},
		{ "question": "簾", "answers": [ "すだれ" ], "comment": "bamboo screen; rattan blind\nbamboo mat (for rolling sushi)" },
		{ "question": "籠球", "answers": [ "バスケットボール" ], "comment": "basketball" },
		{ "question": "米西西皮", "answers": [ "ミシシッピ" ]},
		{ "question": "粗描", "answers": [ "スケッチ" ], "comment": "rough sketch" },
		{ "question": "精霊蝗", "answers": [ "しょうりょうばった" ]},
		{ "question": "糸葱", "answers": [ "あさつき" ]},
		{ "question": "糸魚", "answers": [ "いとよ" ], "comment": "three-spined stickleback (Gasterosteus aculeatus)" },
		{ "question": "約色弗", "answers": [ "ヨセフ" ]},
		{ "question": "紅娘", "answers": [ "てんとうむし" ]},
		{ "question": "紅小灰蝶", "answers": [ "べにしじみ" ]},
		{ "question": "紅葉", "answers": [ "もみじ" ], "comment": "autumn colours; fall colors; leaves changing color (colour)\nleaves turning red; red leaves\n(Japanese) maple (Acer japonicum)\nvenison" },
		{ "question": "紋白蝶", "answers": [ "もんしろちょう" ], "comment": "small cabbage white butterfly (Pieris rapae)" },
		{ "question": "紐瀬流", "answers": [ "ニュージャージー" ]},
		{ "question": "紐育", "answers": [ "ニューヨーク" ], "comment": "New York (US state, city)" },
		{ "question": "紙魚", "answers": [ "しみ" ], "comment": "true bristletail (any insect of order Thysanura, esp. of family Lepismatidae)\nOriental silverfish (Ctenolepisma villosa)\nsomeone who is unable to apply what they have read" },
		{ "question": "素人", "answers": [ "しろうと" ], "comment": "amateur; layman; ordinary person; novice\nrespectable woman (not a prostitute, hostess, geisha, etc.)\nunlicensed prostitute" },
		{ "question": "素描", "answers": [ "デッサン" ], "comment": "drawing; sketch\noutline; summary; synopsis\nuncolored sketch; line sketch; rough sketch" },
		{ "question": "素見", "answers": [ "ひやかし" ], "comment": "teasing; chaffing; raillery; ridicule; jeering\nmerely asking the price; just looking at goods; window-shopping; browsing\nwindow-shopping; browsing" },
		{ "question": "紫蘇", "answers": [ "しそ" ], "comment": "shiso (Perilla frutescens var. crispa); perilla; beefsteak plant" },
		{ "question": "紫陽花", "answers": [ "あじさい" ], "comment": "bigleaf hydrangea (Hydrangea macrophylla); French hydrangea" },
		{ "question": "絣", "answers": [ "かすり" ], "comment": "splash pattern (e.g. on a kimono); dye pattern; kasuri" },
		{ "question": "絨毯", "answers": [ "じゅうたん" ], "comment": "carpet; rug; runner" },
		{ "question": "絨緞", "answers": [ "じゅうたん" ], "comment": "carpet; rug; runner" },
		{ "question": "綬鶏", "answers": [ "じゅけい" ]},
		{ "question": "維納", "answers": [ "ウィーン" ], "comment": "Vienna" },
		{ "question": "縞味", "answers": [ "しまあじ" ], "comment": "garganey (Anas querquedula)" },
		{ "question": "縞蛇", "answers": [ "しまへび" ], "comment": "Japanese four-lined ratsnake (Elaphe quadrivirgata); Japanese striped snake" },
		{ "question": "縞馬", "answers": [ "しまうま" ], "comment": "zebra" },
		{ "question": "繁縷", "answers": [ "はこべ" ], "comment": "chickweed; stitchwort (Stellaria sp.)" },
		{ "question": "罌粟", "answers": [ "けし" ], "comment": "poppy (Papaver somniferum)" },
		{ "question": "羅府", "answers": [ "ロサンゼルス" ]},
		{ "question": "羅馬", "answers": [ "ローマ" ], "comment": "Rome" },
		{ "question": "羅馬尼亜", "answers": [ "ルーマニア" ], "comment": "Romania; Rumania" },
		{ "question": "羊栖菜", "answers": [ "ひじき" ], "comment": "hijiki (dark edible seaweed usu. sold in dried black strips; Hizikia fusiformis)" },
		{ "question": "羊歯", "answers": [ "しだ" ], "comment": "fern (esp. species Gleichenia japonica); fernery" },
		{ "question": "羚羊", "answers": [ "かもしか" ], "comment": "antelope\nserow; wild goat" },
		{ "question": "翌檜", "answers": [ "あすなろ" ], "comment": "hiba false arborvitae (species of cypress, Thujopsis dolabrata)" },
		{ "question": "翡翠", "answers": [ "かわせみ" ], "comment": "kingfisher (esp. the common kingfisher, Alcedo atthis)\njade (gem)\nbeautiful lustrous colour similar to that of the kingfisher's feathers" },
		{ "question": "翻車魚", "answers": [ "まんぼう" ], "comment": "ocean sunfish (Mola mola)" },
		{ "question": "耶蘇", "answers": [ "イエス" ], "comment": "Christ" },
		{ "question": "聖土奴嗷", "answers": [ "サントドミンゴ" ]},
		{ "question": "聖市", "answers": [ "サンパウロ" ]},
		{ "question": "聖林", "answers": [ "ハリウッド" ], "comment": "Hollywood" },
		{ "question": "聖路易", "answers": [ "セントルイス" ]},
		{ "question": "肉汁", "answers": [ "スープ" ], "comment": "meat soup; bouillon; juices (from grilled meat); gravy" },
		{ "question": "肌理", "answers": [ "きめ" ], "comment": "texture (e.g. skin, fabric)\ngrain (e.g. wood)\ndetail" },
		{ "question": "肘", "answers": [ "ひじ" ], "comment": "elbow" },
		{ "question": "肱", "answers": [ "ひじ" ], "comment": "elbow\narm (esp. upper arm)\ncounter used to measure the thickness of round objects" },
		{ "question": "背黄青鸚哥", "answers": [ "せきせいいんこ" ], "comment": "budgerigar (Melopsittacus undulatus); common pet parakeet; shell parakeet; budgie" },
		{ "question": "胝", "answers": [ "たこ" ], "comment": "callus; callosity; corn" },
		{ "question": "胞子嚢", "answers": [ "ほうしのう" ], "comment": "sporangium" },
		{ "question": "胡坐", "answers": [ "あぐら" ], "comment": "sitting cross-legged (i.e. Indian style)" },
		{ "question": "胡床", "answers": [ "あぐら" ], "comment": "sitting cross-legged (i.e. Indian style)" },
		{ "question": "胡桃", "answers": [ "くるみ" ], "comment": "walnut (Juglans spp., esp. Juglans regia)" },
		{ "question": "胡瓜", "answers": [ "きゅうり" ], "comment": "cucumber (Cucumis sativus)" },
		{ "question": "胡蜂", "answers": [ "すずめばち" ], "comment": "hornet; yellow jacket; wasp (of subfamily Vespinae)\nAsian giant hornet (Vespa mandarinia); yak-killer hornet" },
		{ "question": "胡頽子", "answers": [ "ぐみ" ], "comment": "oleaster (any plant of genus Elaeagnus); silverberry (US)" },
		{ "question": "胼胝", "answers": [ "たこ" ], "comment": "callus; callosity; corn" },
		{ "question": "腮", "answers": [ "えら" ], "comment": "chin; jaw\ngills; branchia\nangle of the mandible; gonial angle\nchin; jaw\ngills; branchia" },
		{ "question": "膃肭臍", "answers": [ "おっとせい" ], "comment": "fur seal (esp. the northern fur seal, Callorhinus ursinus); Alaskan fur seal" },
		{ "question": "膝", "answers": [ "ひざ" ], "comment": "knee\nlap; knee and thigh (while sitting)" },
		{ "question": "膿", "answers": [ "うみ" ], "comment": "pus" },
		{ "question": "臂", "answers": [ "ひじ" ], "comment": "elbow" },
		{ "question": "臍", "answers": [ "へそ" ], "comment": "navel; belly button\nprotrusion or depression in the middle of an object\ncenter; centre; most important part; main point" },
		{ "question": "自棄", "answers": [ "やけ" ], "comment": "desperation; despair; self-abandonment" },
		{ "question": "自鳴琴", "answers": [ "オルゴール" ], "comment": "musical box; music box" },
		{ "question": "臭橙", "answers": [ "だいだい" ], "comment": "kabosu (type of citrus fruit) (Citrus sphaerocarpa)" },
		{ "question": "舎路", "answers": [ "シアトル" ]},
		{ "question": "舞舞被", "answers": [ "まいまいかぶり" ]},
		{ "question": "舷梯", "answers": [ "タラップ" ], "comment": "gangway (ladder)" },
		{ "question": "船渠", "answers": [ "ドック" ], "comment": "dock" },
		{ "question": "船虫", "answers": [ "ふなむし" ], "comment": "wharf roach (species of isopod closely related to the sea slater; Ligia exotica)" },
		{ "question": "良富羅多", "answers": [ "ラプラタ" ]},
		{ "question": "艾", "answers": [ "よもぎ" ], "comment": "Japanese mugwort (Artemisia princeps, Artemisia indica var. maximowiczii)\ngeneral term for plants in the Artemisia genus; mugwort; sagebrush; wormwood\nmoxa\nJapanese mugwort" },
		{ "question": "芋虫", "answers": [ "いもむし" ], "comment": "hornworm (caterpillar of a hawk moth); (hairless) caterpillar" },
		{ "question": "芍薬", "answers": [ "しゃくやく" ], "comment": "Chinese peony (Paeonia lactiflora)" },
		{ "question": "芒", "answers": [ "すすき" ], "comment": "Japanese pampas grass (Miscanthus sinensis); silver grass; zebra grass\narista; awn; (grain) beard" },
		{ "question": "芥子", "answers": [ "けし" ], "comment": "mustard\npoppy (Papaver somniferum)" },
		{ "question": "芥箱", "answers": [ "ごみばこ" ], "comment": "garbage can; garbage box; rubbish bin; trash can; dust bin; dustbin" },
		{ "question": "芬蘭", "answers": [ "フィンランド" ], "comment": "Finland" },
		{ "question": "花梨", "answers": [ "かりん" ], "comment": "Burmese rosewood (Pterocarpus indicus); angsana; amboyna; amboina\nflowering quince (of genus Chaenomeles) (Pseudocydonia sinensis); Chinese quince (Chaenomeles sinensis)\nquince (Cydonia oblonga)" },
		{ "question": "花櫚", "answers": [ "かりん" ], "comment": "Burmese rosewood (Pterocarpus indicus); angsana; amboyna; amboina\nflowering quince (of genus Chaenomeles) (Pseudocydonia sinensis); Chinese quince (Chaenomeles sinensis)\nquince (Cydonia oblonga)" },
		{ "question": "花潜", "answers": [ "はなむぐり" ], "comment": "flower chafer (any flower beetle of tribe Cetoniini)\nEucetonia pilifera (flower chafer species of tribe Cetoniini)" },
		{ "question": "芹", "answers": [ "せり" ], "comment": "Java water dropwort (Oenanthe javanica); Japanese parsley" },
		{ "question": "苔", "answers": [ "こけ" ], "comment": "moss\nshort plants resembling moss (incl. other bryophytes, lichens, very small spermatophytes, etc.)" },
		{ "question": "若布", "answers": [ "わかめ" ], "comment": "wakame (species of edible brown seaweed, Undaria pinnatifida)" },
		{ "question": "若鷺", "answers": [ "わかさぎ" ], "comment": "Japanese pond smelt (Hypomesus nipponensis)" },
		{ "question": "英吉利", "answers": [ "イギリス" ], "comment": "Great Britain; United Kingdom" },
		{ "question": "英蘭", "answers": [ "イングランド" ], "comment": "England\nGreat Britain and the Netherlands" },
		{ "question": "苳", "answers": [ "ふき" ], "comment": "giant butterbur (Petasites japonicus); Japanese sweet coltsfoot" },
		{ "question": "苺", "answers": [ "いちご" ], "comment": "strawberry (esp. the garden strawberry, Fragaria x ananassa)" },
		{ "question": "茄", "answers": [ "なす" ], "comment": "eggplant (Solanum melongena); aubergine" },
		{ "question": "茄子", "answers": [ "なす" ], "comment": "eggplant (Solanum melongena); aubergine" },
		{ "question": "茅蜩", "answers": [ "ひぐらし" ], "comment": "evening cicada (Tanna japonensis)" },
		{ "question": "茗荷", "answers": [ "みょうが" ], "comment": "Japanese ginger (Zingiber mioga)" },
		{ "question": "茘枝", "answers": [ "れいし" ], "comment": "litchi (Nephelium litchi); lychee; lichee; litchi nut\nbitter melon (Momordica charantia); bitter gourd\nThais bronni (species of muricid gastropod)" },
		{ "question": "茜", "answers": [ "あかね" ], "comment": "madder (esp. Japanese madder, Rubia argyi)\nmadder (red color)" },
		{ "question": "茱萸", "answers": [ "ぐみ" ], "comment": "oleaster (any plant of genus Elaeagnus); silverberry (US)" },
		{ "question": "莎草", "answers": [ "かやつりぐさ" ], "comment": "galingale (any plant of genus Cyperus, esp. species Cyperus microiria)\nnut grass (Cyperus rotundus)\nPacific island flatsedge (Cyperus cyperoides)" },
		{ "question": "莓", "answers": [ "いちご" ], "comment": "strawberry (esp. the garden strawberry, Fragaria x ananassa)" },
		{ "question": "莨", "answers": [ "たばこ" ], "comment": "tobacco; cigarette; cigaret; cigar\ntobacco plant (Nicotiana tabacum)" },
		{ "question": "莫大小", "answers": [ "メリヤス" ], "comment": "knitting; hosiery; knitted goods" },
		{ "question": "莫差特", "answers": [ "モーツァルト" ]},
		{ "question": "莫斯科", "answers": [ "モスクワ" ], "comment": "Moscow" },
		{ "question": "莫臥児", "answers": [ "モンゴル" ], "comment": "lace; lacing braid\nchenille yarn\ntinsel\npipe cleaner; fibre, paper, etc. twisted between a pair of wires" },
		{ "question": "菅", "answers": [ "すげ" ], "comment": "sedge (Cyperaceae spp., esp. members of genus Carex)" },
		{ "question": "菎蒻", "answers": [ "こんにゃく" ], "comment": "konnyaku (Amorphophallus konjac); konjac; devil's tongue\nkonnyaku jelly; konjac jelly; devil's tongue jelly" },
		{ "question": "菖蒲", "answers": [ "あやめ" ], "comment": "sweet flag (Acorus calamus); calamus\nJapanese iris (Iris ensata var. ensata)\niris (flower)\nSiberian iris (Iris sanguinea)\nsweet flag (Acorus calamus); calamus" },
		{ "question": "菜単", "answers": [ "メニュー" ], "comment": "menu (at a Chinese restaurant)" },
		{ "question": "菜蕗", "answers": [ "ふき" ], "comment": "giant butterbur (Petasites japonicus); Japanese sweet coltsfoot" },
		{ "question": "菟葵", "answers": [ "いそぎんちゃく" ], "comment": "sea anemone" },
		{ "question": "菠薐草", "answers": [ "ほうれんそう" ], "comment": "spinach" },
		{ "question": "菫", "answers": [ "すみれ" ], "comment": "violet (any flower of genus Viola, esp. the Fuji dawn, Viola mandshurica)" },
		{ "question": "華盛頓", "answers": [ "ワシントン" ], "comment": "Washington, DC (capital of the United States of America)\nWashington (US state)" },
		{ "question": "菱喰", "answers": [ "ひしくい" ]},
		{ "question": "萵苣", "answers": [ "ちしゃ" ], "comment": "lettuce" },
		{ "question": "落機", "answers": [ "ロッキー" ]},
		{ "question": "落葉松", "answers": [ "からまつ" ], "comment": "(Japanese) larch (Larix leptolepis, Larix kaempferi)" },
		{ "question": "葉虫", "answers": [ "はむし" ], "comment": "leaf beetle (of family Chrysomelidae)" },
		{ "question": "葉鶏頭", "answers": [ "はげいとう" ], "comment": "tampala; Joseph's coat; Amaranthus tricolor" },
		{ "question": "葛", "answers": [ "くず" ], "comment": "kudzu (Pueraria montana); Japanese arrowroot\nChinese moonseed (Sinomenium acutum)\ncreeping plant; creeper" },
		{ "question": "葡萄", "answers": [ "ぶどう" ], "comment": "grape; grapevine" },
		{ "question": "葡萄牙", "answers": [ "ポルトガル" ], "comment": "Portugal" },
		{ "question": "葡萄酒", "answers": [ "ワイン" ], "comment": "(grape) wine" },
		{ "question": "葦五位", "answers": [ "よしごい" ], "comment": "yellow bittern (Ixobrychus sinensis)" },
		{ "question": "葦切", "answers": [ "よしきり" ], "comment": "reed warbler (esp. the great reed warbler, but also the black-browed reed warbler)" },
		{ "question": "葦登", "answers": [ "よしのぼり" ], "comment": "Amur goby (Rhinogobius brunneus)" },
		{ "question": "葦雀", "answers": [ "よしきり" ], "comment": "reed warbler (esp. the great reed warbler, but also the black-browed reed warbler)" },
		{ "question": "葦鹿", "answers": [ "あしか" ], "comment": "eared seal (esp. the California sea lion, Zalophus californianus); sea lion" },
		{ "question": "葫", "answers": [ "にんにく" ], "comment": "garlic (Allium sativum)\nstrong-smelling edible plant (esp. perennials of the family Liliaceae, e.g. Welsh onion, garlic, wild rocambole, etc.)" },
		{ "question": "葭五位", "answers": [ "よしごい" ]},
		{ "question": "葭切", "answers": [ "よしきり" ], "comment": "reed warbler (esp. the great reed warbler, but also the black-browed reed warbler)" },
		{ "question": "葱", "answers": [ "ねぎ" ], "comment": "Welsh onion (species of scallion, Allium fistulosum); green onion; spring onion" },
		{ "question": "葵", "answers": [ "あおい" ], "comment": "mallow (any plant of family Malvaceae)\nAsarum caulescens (species of wild ginger)\nhollyhock" },
		{ "question": "蒟蒻", "answers": [ "こんにゃく" ], "comment": "konnyaku (Amorphophallus konjac); konjac; devil's tongue\nkonnyaku jelly; konjac jelly; devil's tongue jelly" },
		{ "question": "蒲公英", "answers": [ "たんぽぽ" ], "comment": "dandelion (esp. species Taraxacum platycarpum)" },
		{ "question": "蒲団", "answers": [ "ふとん" ], "comment": "futon (quilted Japanese-style mattress laid out on the floor)\nround cushion used for Zen meditation (traditionally made of woven bulrush leaves)" },
		{ "question": "蓑虫", "answers": [ "みのむし" ], "comment": "bagworm; bagworm moth" },
		{ "question": "蓬", "answers": [ "よもぎ" ], "comment": "Japanese mugwort (Artemisia princeps, Artemisia indica var. maximowiczii)\ngeneral term for plants in the Artemisia genus; mugwort; sagebrush; wormwood" },
		{ "question": "蓮", "answers": [ "はす" ], "comment": "sacred lotus (Nelumbo nucifera); Indian lotus; lotus\nrose of Sharon (Hibiscus syriacus)" },
		{ "question": "蓮根", "answers": [ "れんこん" ], "comment": "lotus root" },
		{ "question": "蓮花", "answers": [ "れんげ" ], "comment": "lotus flower\nChinese milk vetch (Astragalus sinicus)\nchina spoon\nlotus-shaped pedestal for a gravestone" },
		{ "question": "蓮華", "answers": [ "れんげ" ], "comment": "lotus flower\nChinese milk vetch (Astragalus sinicus)\nchina spoon\nlotus-shaped pedestal for a gravestone" },
		{ "question": "蓮角", "answers": [ "れんかく" ], "comment": "jacana (esp. the pheasant-tailed jacana, Hydrophasianus chirurgus); lily-trotter" },
		{ "question": "蓼", "answers": [ "たで" ], "comment": "knotweed (Polygonaceae); jointweed; smartweed\nwater pepper (Persicaria hydropiper)" },
		{ "question": "蕃椒", "answers": [ "とうがらし" ], "comment": "capsicum (Capsicum annuum, esp. the cultivated chili peppers); chili pepper (chile, chilli); cayenne; red pepper\nshichimi pepper" },
		{ "question": "蕃茄", "answers": [ "トマト" ], "comment": "tomato (Solanum lycopersicum)" },
		{ "question": "蕎麦滓", "answers": [ "そばかす" ], "comment": "freckles\nbuckwheat chaff" },
		{ "question": "蕗", "answers": [ "ふき" ], "comment": "giant butterbur (Petasites japonicus); Japanese sweet coltsfoot" },
		{ "question": "蕨", "answers": [ "わらび" ], "comment": "bracken" },
		{ "question": "蕪", "answers": [ "かぶ" ], "comment": "turnip (Brassica rapa)" },
		{ "question": "薄", "answers": [ "すすき" ], "comment": "Japanese pampas grass (Miscanthus sinensis); silver grass; zebra grass\nlight (e.g. colour, color)" },
		{ "question": "薄翅蜉蝣", "answers": [ "うすばかげろう" ]},
		{ "question": "薄荷酒", "answers": [ "ペパーミント" ]},
		{ "question": "薇", "answers": [ "ぜんまい" ], "comment": "royal fern (Osmunda japonica); flowering fern; osmund; fiddlehead fern" },
		{ "question": "薊", "answers": [ "あざみ" ], "comment": "thistle (Cirsium spp.)" },
		{ "question": "薑", "answers": [ "しょうが" ], "comment": "ginger (Zingiber officinale)\nginger (Zingiber officinale)\nJapanese pepper (Zanthoxylum piperitum)" },
		{ "question": "薔薇", "answers": [ "ばら" ], "comment": "rose" },
		{ "question": "薤", "answers": [ "らっきょう" ], "comment": "Japanese leek (Allium chinense); Chinese onion\nsour-sweet pickle of Japanese leek" },
		{ "question": "薩摩芋", "answers": [ "さつまいも" ], "comment": "sweet potato (Ipomoea batatas)" },
		{ "question": "薯蕷芋", "answers": [ "とろろいも" ], "comment": "yam" },
		{ "question": "薺", "answers": [ "なずな" ], "comment": "shepherd's purse (Capsella bursa-pastoris)" },
		{ "question": "藁素坊", "answers": [ "わらすぼ" ]},
		{ "question": "藍子", "answers": [ "あいご" ], "comment": "mottled spinefoot (Siganus fuscescens, species of Western Pacific rabbitfish); dusky rabbitfish; sandy spinefoot" },
		{ "question": "藺草", "answers": [ "いぐさ" ], "comment": "soft rush (Juncus effusus var. decipiens)" },
		{ "question": "蘇丹", "answers": [ "スーダン" ], "comment": "Sudan" },
		{ "question": "蘇士", "answers": [ "スエズ" ]},
		{ "question": "蘇格蘭", "answers": [ "スコットランド" ]},
		{ "question": "蘇素", "answers": [ "スエズ" ]},
		{ "question": "蘇鉄", "answers": [ "そてつ" ], "comment": "sago cycad (Cycas revoluta); king sago palm; sago palm; Japanese sago palm" },
		{ "question": "蘚", "answers": [ "こけ" ], "comment": "moss\nshort plants resembling moss (incl. other bryophytes, lichens, very small spermatophytes, etc.)" },
		{ "question": "蘭", "answers": [ "らん" ], "comment": "orchid\nHolland; The Netherlands\nJapanese yew (Taxus cuspidata)\nwild rocambole (Allium grayi)\nthoroughwort (species of boneset, Eupatorium fortunei)" },
		{ "question": "蘿", "answers": [ "こけ" ], "comment": "moss\nshort plants resembling moss (incl. other bryophytes, lichens, very small spermatophytes, etc.)\nrunning ground pine (species of club moss, Lycopodium clavatum)" },
		{ "question": "虎", "answers": [ "とら" ], "comment": "tiger (Panthera tigris)\ndrunkard; drunk; sot" },
		{ "question": "虎列剌", "answers": [ "コレラ" ], "comment": "cholera" },
		{ "question": "虎魚", "answers": [ "おこぜ" ], "comment": "stingfish; scorpion fish; stonefish" },
		{ "question": "虱", "answers": [ "しらみ" ], "comment": "louse (esp. a sucking louse); lice" },
		{ "question": "虻", "answers": [ "あぶ" ], "comment": "horsefly; gadfly" },
		{ "question": "蚊", "answers": [ "か" ], "comment": "mosquito" },
		{ "question": "蚊帳吊草", "answers": [ "かやつりぐさ" ], "comment": "galingale (any plant of genus Cyperus, esp. species Cyperus microiria)\nnut grass (Cyperus rotundus)" },
		{ "question": "蚊母鳥", "answers": [ "よたか" ], "comment": "grey nightjar (Caprimulgus indicus)\nnightjar (any bird of family Caprimulgidae); goatsucker" },
		{ "question": "蚌", "answers": [ "はまぐり" ], "comment": "common orient clam (Meretrix lusoria)" },
		{ "question": "蚕", "answers": [ "かいこ" ], "comment": "silkworm (Bombyx mori)" },
		{ "question": "蚤", "answers": [ "のみ" ], "comment": "flea" },
		{ "question": "蚯蚓", "answers": [ "みみず" ], "comment": "earthworm" },
		{ "question": "蚰蜒", "answers": [ "げじ" ], "comment": "house centipede (Scutigeromorpha spp.)\ncontemptible person; skunk; wretch; louse" },
		{ "question": "蛆", "answers": [ "うじ" ], "comment": "maggot; larva; grub" },
		{ "question": "蛍", "answers": [ "ほたる" ], "comment": "firefly (Luciola cruciata); lightning bug; glowworm" },
		{ "question": "蛙", "answers": [ "かえる" ], "comment": "frog\nkajika frog (Buergeria buergeri)" },
		{ "question": "蛞蝓", "answers": [ "なめくじ" ], "comment": "slug" },
		{ "question": "蛤", "answers": [ "はまぐり" ], "comment": "common orient clam (Meretrix lusoria)\nfrog\nkajika frog (Buergeria buergeri)" },
		{ "question": "蛭", "answers": [ "ひる" ], "comment": "leech" },
		{ "question": "蛸", "answers": [ "たこ" ], "comment": "octopus" },
		{ "question": "蛾", "answers": [ "が" ], "comment": "moth" },
		{ "question": "蜂", "answers": [ "はち" ], "comment": "bee; wasp; hornet" },
		{ "question": "蜂熊", "answers": [ "はちくま" ], "comment": "crested honey buzzard (Pernis ptilorhynchus); Oriental honey buzzard; pern" },
		{ "question": "蜂角鷹", "answers": [ "はちくま" ], "comment": "crested honey buzzard (Pernis ptilorhynchus); Oriental honey buzzard; pern" },
		{ "question": "蜂鳥", "answers": [ "はちどり" ], "comment": "hummingbird (Trochilidae family)" },
		{ "question": "蜆", "answers": [ "しじみ" ], "comment": "basket clam (Corbiculidae spp.); freshwater clam; freshwater mussel" },
		{ "question": "蜈蚣", "answers": [ "むかで" ], "comment": "centipede" },
		{ "question": "蜉蝣", "answers": [ "かげろう" ], "comment": "mayfly; ephemeropteran\nephemerality (of human life)\ndragonfly; damselfly" },
		{ "question": "蜘蛛", "answers": [ "くも" ], "comment": "spider" },
		{ "question": "蜜柑", "answers": [ "みかん" ], "comment": "mandarin orange (esp. the satsuma mandarin, Citrus unshiu)" },
		{ "question": "蜥蜴", "answers": [ "とかげ" ], "comment": "lizard\nskink lizard (Scincidae spp.)" },
		{ "question": "蜩", "answers": [ "ひぐらし" ], "comment": "evening cicada (Tanna japonensis)" },
		{ "question": "蜻蛉", "answers": [ "かげろう","とんぼ" ], "comment": "dragonfly; damselfly" },
		{ "question": "蝉", "answers": [ "せみ" ], "comment": "cicada; locust\nsmall-sized pulley" },
		{ "question": "蝗", "answers": [ "いなご","ばった" ], "comment": "rice grasshopper (of genus Oxya)\ngrasshopper; locust (of family Catantopidae)\ngrasshopper; locust (of superfamily Acridoidea)\nrice pest" },
		{ "question": "蝗虫", "answers": [ "ばった" ], "comment": "grasshopper; locust (of superfamily Acridoidea)\nrice grasshopper (of genus Oxya)" },
		{ "question": "蝙蝠", "answers": [ "こうもり" ], "comment": "bat (Chiroptera spp.)\numbrella\nopportunist; turncoat" },
		{ "question": "蝦", "answers": [ "えび" ], "comment": "frog\nkajika frog (Buergeria buergeri)\nprawn; shrimp; lobster; crayfish" },
		{ "question": "蝦根", "answers": [ "えびね" ], "comment": "Calanthe discolor (species of orchid)" },
		{ "question": "蝦虎魚", "answers": [ "はぜ" ], "comment": "goby (fish)\nyellowfin goby (Acanthogobius flavimanus)" },
		{ "question": "蝦蛄", "answers": [ "しゃこ" ], "comment": "mantis shrimp (any marine crustacean of order Stomatopoda, esp. the species Oratosquilla oratoria)" },
		{ "question": "蝦蟇", "answers": [ "がま" ], "comment": "toad (esp. the Japanese toad, Bufo japonicus)" },
		{ "question": "蝨", "answers": [ "しらみ" ], "comment": "louse (esp. a sucking louse); lice" },
		{ "question": "蝮", "answers": [ "まむし" ], "comment": "pit viper (esp. the mamushi, Gloydius blomhoffi)" },
		{ "question": "蝶", "answers": [ "ちょう" ], "comment": "butterfly" },
		{ "question": "蝶鮫", "answers": [ "ちょうざめ" ], "comment": "sturgeon (esp. the green sturgeon, Acipenser medirostris)" },
		{ "question": "蝸牛", "answers": [ "かたつむり" ], "comment": "snail\ncochlea" },
		{ "question": "蝸牛被", "answers": [ "まいまいかぶり" ]},
		{ "question": "螳螂", "answers": [ "かまきり" ], "comment": "praying mantis (esp. the narrow-winged mantis, Tenodera angustipennis)" },
		{ "question": "螺子", "answers": [ "ネジ" ], "comment": "screw\nkey (of a clock, watch, etc.); spring (of a clock, watch, etc.)" },
		{ "question": "螻蛄", "answers": [ "けら" ], "comment": "mole cricket (esp. the Oriental mole cricket, Gryllotalpa orientalis)\nbeing penniless; being broke" },
		{ "question": "螽斯", "answers": [ "きりぎりす" ], "comment": "Japanese katydid (Gampsocleis buergeri)\nkatydid; bush-cricket (Tettigoniidae); long-horned grasshopper\ncricket" },
		{ "question": "蟇", "answers": [ "がま" ], "comment": "toad (esp. the Japanese toad, Bufo japonicus)" },
		{ "question": "蟋蟀", "answers": [ "きりぎりす","こおろぎ" ], "comment": "cricket (Gryllidae spp.)\nany insect that chirps in autumn\nJapanese katydid (Gampsocleis buergeri)\nkatydid; bush-cricket (Tettigoniidae); long-horned grasshopper\ncricket" },
		{ "question": "蟷螂", "answers": [ "かまきり" ], "comment": "praying mantis (esp. the narrow-winged mantis, Tenodera angustipennis)" },
		{ "question": "蟹", "answers": [ "かに" ], "comment": "crab" },
		{ "question": "蟻", "answers": [ "あり" ], "comment": "ant" },
		{ "question": "蟻食", "answers": [ "ありくい" ], "comment": "anteater" },
		{ "question": "蠅", "answers": [ "はえ" ], "comment": "fly (of infraorder Muscomorpha)\nperson of no worth; pisher; scrub" },
		{ "question": "蠍", "answers": [ "さそり" ], "comment": "scorpion (Scorpiones spp.)" },
		{ "question": "蠹魚", "answers": [ "しみ" ]},
		{ "question": "衣魚", "answers": [ "しみ" ], "comment": "true bristletail (any insect of order Thysanura, esp. of family Lepismatidae)\nOriental silverfish (Ctenolepisma villosa)\nsomeone who is unable to apply what they have read" },
		{ "question": "襟巻蜥蜴", "answers": [ "えりまきとかげ" ], "comment": "frilled lizard (Chlamydosaurus kingii); frill-necked lizard" },
		{ "question": "襯衣", "answers": [ "シャツ" ], "comment": "underwear" },
		{ "question": "西比利亜", "answers": [ "シベリア" ]},
		{ "question": "西班牙", "answers": [ "スペイン" ], "comment": "Spain" },
		{ "question": "西瓜", "answers": [ "すいか" ], "comment": "watermelon (Citrullus lanatus)" },
		{ "question": "西貢", "answers": [ "サイゴン" ], "comment": "Saigon" },
		{ "question": "角布", "answers": [ "ケープタウン" ]},
		{ "question": "角灯", "answers": [ "ランタン" ], "comment": "square hand-lantern" },
		{ "question": "角鴟", "answers": [ "みみずく" ], "comment": "horned owl" },
		{ "question": "許婚", "answers": [ "いいなずけ" ], "comment": "fiance; fiancee" },
		{ "question": "許嫁", "answers": [ "いいなずけ" ], "comment": "fiance; fiancee" },
		{ "question": "諾威", "answers": [ "ノルウェー" ], "comment": "Norway" },
		{ "question": "譲葉", "answers": [ "ゆずりは" ], "comment": "false daphne (Daphniphyllum macropodum); yuzuriha" },
		{ "question": "護謨", "answers": [ "ゴム" ], "comment": "gum; rubber\neraser\ncondom" },
		{ "question": "豌豆", "answers": [ "えんどう" ], "comment": "green peas" },
		{ "question": "豚脂", "answers": [ "ラード" ], "comment": "lard; pig fat" },
		{ "question": "象虫", "answers": [ "ぞうむし" ], "comment": "weevil; snout beetle" },
		{ "question": "象鼻虫", "answers": [ "ぞうむし" ]},
		{ "question": "豪猪", "answers": [ "やまあらし" ], "comment": "porcupine (any mammal of suborder Hystricomorpha)" },
		{ "question": "豹", "answers": [ "ひょう" ], "comment": "leopard (Panthera pardus); panther" },
		{ "question": "貂", "answers": [ "てん" ], "comment": "Japanese marten (Martes melampus)\nmarten (any arboreal weasel-like mammal of genus Martes)" },
		{ "question": "貘", "answers": [ "ばく" ], "comment": "tapir (Tapirus spp.)\nmo; mythological Chinese chimera similar to a tapir, said to devour bad dreams" },
		{ "question": "貝", "answers": [ "ばい" ], "comment": "shellfish\nseashell; shell\nJapanese babylon (species of shelled mollusk, Babylonia japonica); Japanese ivory shell\nspinning top (traditionally made from a Japanese babylon shell)" },
		{ "question": "貝多芬", "answers": [ "ベートーベン" ]},
		{ "question": "貯古齢糖", "answers": [ "チョコレート" ]},
		{ "question": "貴婦人", "answers": [ "レディ" ], "comment": "lady" },
		{ "question": "費府", "answers": [ "フィラデルフィア" ]},
		{ "question": "賓", "answers": [ "まろうど" ], "comment": "visitor from afar; guest\nvisitor from afar\njoy-bringing spirit from the divine realms" },
		{ "question": "賞牌", "answers": [ "メダル" ], "comment": "medal" },
		{ "question": "賽子", "answers": [ "さいころ" ], "comment": "dice; die" },
		{ "question": "赤保留古", "answers": [ "アカプルコ" ]},
		{ "question": "赤楝蛇", "answers": [ "やまかがし" ]},
		{ "question": "越列機", "answers": [ "エレキ" ]},
		{ "question": "越南", "answers": [ "ベトナム" ], "comment": "Vietnam" },
		{ "question": "路照", "answers": [ "ロッテルダム" ]},
		{ "question": "踵", "answers": [ "かかと" ], "comment": "heel (of foot, shoe, stocking, etc.)" },
		{ "question": "蹴球", "answers": [ "フットボール" ], "comment": "football (incl. soccer, rugby, American football, etc.; esp. used for soccer)" },
		{ "question": "躑躅", "answers": [ "つつじ" ], "comment": "azalea (Rhododendron spp.)" },
		{ "question": "車前草", "answers": [ "おおばこ" ], "comment": "plantain (esp. Asian plantain, Plantago asiatica)" },
		{ "question": "軍鶏", "answers": [ "シャモ" ], "comment": "game fowl; gamecock" },
		{ "question": "軽衫", "answers": [ "カルサン" ], "comment": "hakama fashioned in the style of the pantaloons worn by the Portuguese" },
		{ "question": "軽鴨", "answers": [ "かるがも" ], "comment": "spot-billed duck (Anas poecilorhyncha)" },
		{ "question": "轆轤", "answers": [ "ろくろ" ], "comment": "lathe\npotter's wheel\nwindlass; pulley" },
		{ "question": "轡虫", "answers": [ "くつわむし" ], "comment": "Mecopoda nipponensis (species of katydid)" },
		{ "question": "辣韭", "answers": [ "らっきょう" ], "comment": "Japanese leek (Allium chinense); Chinese onion\nsour-sweet pickle of Japanese leek" },
		{ "question": "辣韮", "answers": [ "らっきょう" ], "comment": "Japanese leek (Allium chinense); Chinese onion\nsour-sweet pickle of Japanese leek" },
		{ "question": "追河", "answers": [ "おいかわ" ], "comment": "freshwater minnow; pale chub (Zacco platypus)" },
		{ "question": "送球", "answers": [ "ハンドボール" ], "comment": "throwing a ball\nhandball" },
		{ "question": "通草", "answers": [ "あけび" ], "comment": "chocolate-vine (Akebia quinata); fiveleaf; fiveleaf akebia\nfruit of the akebia" },
		{ "question": "遍羅", "answers": [ "べら" ], "comment": "wrasse (any fish of family Labridae)" },
		{ "question": "那坡利", "answers": [ "ナポリ" ]},
		{ "question": "那波列翁", "answers": [ "ナポレオン" ]},
		{ "question": "部屋重良", "answers": [ "ベネズエラ" ]},
		{ "question": "郭公", "answers": [ "かっこう","ほととぎす" ], "comment": "common cuckoo (Cuculus canorus)\nlesser cuckoo (Cuculus poliocephalus)" },
		{ "question": "都伯林", "answers": [ "ダブリン" ]},
		{ "question": "鄂木斯克", "answers": [ "オムスク" ]},
		{ "question": "鄂霍次克", "answers": [ "オホーツク" ]},
		{ "question": "酒杯", "answers": [ "コップ" ], "comment": "sake cup; wine cup" },
		{ "question": "酒精", "answers": [ "アルコール" ], "comment": "(ethyl) alcohol; spirits of wine" },
		{ "question": "酢橘", "answers": [ "すだち" ], "comment": "sudachi (species of Japanese citrus, Citrus sudachi)" },
		{ "question": "酸漿", "answers": [ "ほおずき" ], "comment": "ground cherry (Physalis alkekengi var. franchetii); husk tomato; Chinese lantern plant" },
		{ "question": "里斯本", "answers": [ "リスボン" ]},
		{ "question": "野羊", "answers": [ "やぎ" ], "comment": "goat" },
		{ "question": "金亀子", "answers": [ "こがねむし" ], "comment": "scarabaeid beetle\nMimela splendens (metallic-green scarabaeid beetle)" },
		{ "question": "金木犀", "answers": [ "きんもくせい" ], "comment": "fragrant olive (Osmanthus fragrans var. aurantiacus)" },
		{ "question": "金盞花", "answers": [ "きんせんか" ], "comment": "marigold; Calendula officinalis" },
		{ "question": "金糸雀", "answers": [ "カナリア" ], "comment": "canary (esp. the island canary, Serinus canaria)" },
		{ "question": "金花虫", "answers": [ "はむし" ], "comment": "leaf beetle (of family Chrysomelidae)" },
		{ "question": "釘", "answers": [ "くぎ" ], "comment": "nail (i.e. small metal spike)" },
		{ "question": "針魚", "answers": [ "はりよ" ], "comment": "Japanese halfbeak (species of fish with elongated lower jaw) (Hemiramphus sajori); stickleback\nGasterosteus microcephalus (species of stickleback)" },
		{ "question": "釦", "answers": [ "ボタン" ], "comment": "button" },
		{ "question": "鉄漿", "answers": [ "おはぐろ" ], "comment": "tooth blackening\ntooth-blackening dye\ntooth blackening" },
		{ "question": "鉈", "answers": [ "なた" ], "comment": "hatchet; traditional Japanese edged tool with short handle and wide blade" },
		{ "question": "鉋", "answers": [ "かんな" ], "comment": "plane (for working with wood)" },
		{ "question": "鉞", "answers": [ "まさかり" ], "comment": "broadaxe; battle axe" },
		{ "question": "鉦", "answers": [ "かね" ], "comment": "gong; handbell" },
		{ "question": "鉾", "answers": [ "ほこ" ], "comment": "long-handled Chinese spear; lance; pike\nweapon; arms\ngrip of a bow" },
		{ "question": "銀杏", "answers": [ "いちょう" ], "comment": "ginkgo (Ginkgo biloba); gingko; maidenhair tree\nginkgo nut; gingko nut" },
		{ "question": "鋏", "answers": [ "はさみ" ], "comment": "scissors; shears; clippers\nhole punch\npincers; nippers; pliers" },
		{ "question": "鋒", "answers": [ "ほこ" ], "comment": "point of spear; spearhead\nbrunt; aim of attack; force of argument\npoint (of a sword, etc.)\npointed verbal attack\nlong-handled Chinese spear; lance; pike\nweapon; arms\ngrip of a bow" },
		{ "question": "鋤", "answers": [ "すき" ], "comment": "spade\nplough; plow" },
		{ "question": "鋲", "answers": [ "びょう" ], "comment": "rivet; tack; thumbtack; drawing-pin; hobnail" },
		{ "question": "錐", "answers": [ "きり" ], "comment": "drill; gimlet; awl; auger\ncone; pyramid" },
		{ "question": "錘", "answers": [ "おもり" ], "comment": "weight\nsinker (fishing)\nspindle\ncounter for spindles\nweight (of a fishing net)" },
		{ "question": "錨", "answers": [ "いかり" ], "comment": "anchor" },
		{ "question": "錫蘭", "answers": [ "セイロン" ], "comment": "Ceylon" },
		{ "question": "錻力", "answers": [ "ブリキ" ], "comment": "tin plate" },
		{ "question": "鍍金", "answers": [ "メッキ" ], "comment": "plating (chrome, gold, silver, etc.); coating; gilding; gilt\npretense; pretence; simulation" },
		{ "question": "鍔", "answers": [ "つば" ], "comment": "guard on sword, polearms, etc.; flange\nbrim; visor (e.g. of a hat)" },
		{ "question": "鍬", "answers": [ "くわ" ], "comment": "hoe" },
		{ "question": "鍬形虫", "answers": [ "くわがたむし" ], "comment": "stag beetle" },
		{ "question": "鎌切", "answers": [ "かまきり" ], "comment": "praying mantis (esp. the narrow-winged mantis, Tenodera angustipennis)" },
		{ "question": "鎚", "answers": [ "つち" ]},
		{ "question": "鏝", "answers": [ "こて" ], "comment": "flat-iron\nsoldering iron\ncrimper; curling tongs\ntrowel" },
		{ "question": "鐔", "answers": [ "つば" ], "comment": "guard on sword, polearms, etc.; flange\nbrim; visor (e.g. of a hat)" },
		{ "question": "鐘", "answers": [ "かね" ], "comment": "bell (often a large hanging bell); chime" },
		{ "question": "鑢", "answers": [ "やすり" ], "comment": "file; rasp" },
		{ "question": "鑿", "answers": [ "のみ" ], "comment": "chisel" },
		{ "question": "長押", "answers": [ "なげし" ], "comment": "beam running between columns in traditional Japanese architecture, esp. within Japanese-style rooms" },
		{ "question": "門得尓", "answers": [ "メンデル" ]},
		{ "question": "閔行", "answers": [ "ミュンヘン" ]},
		{ "question": "閣龍", "answers": [ "コロンブス" ]},
		{ "question": "阿古屋貝", "answers": [ "あこやがい" ], "comment": "Marten's pearl oyster (Pinctada fucata martensii); Akoya pearl oyster" },
		{ "question": "阿弗利加", "answers": [ "アフリカ" ], "comment": "Africa" },
		{ "question": "阿房鳥", "answers": [ "あほうどり" ], "comment": "albatross (esp. the short-tailed albatross, Phoebastria albatrus)" },
		{ "question": "阿比", "answers": [ "あび" ], "comment": "red-throated loon (Gavia stellata)" },
		{ "question": "阿爾卑斯", "answers": [ "アルプス" ]},
		{ "question": "阿爾及", "answers": [ "アルジェリア" ], "comment": "Algeria" },
		{ "question": "阿爾泰", "answers": [ "アルタイ" ]},
		{ "question": "阿羅斯加", "answers": [ "アラスカ" ]},
		{ "question": "阿蘭陀", "answers": [ "オランダ" ], "comment": "Holland; The Netherlands" },
		{ "question": "階子", "answers": [ "はしご" ], "comment": "ladder\nstairs\ngoing to several places in succession (e.g. barhopping)" },
		{ "question": "障泥", "answers": [ "あおり" ], "comment": "saddle flap" },
		{ "question": "隠元豆", "answers": [ "いんげんまめ" ], "comment": "common bean (Phaseolus vulgaris); kidney bean; navy bean; wax bean; green bean; string bean; French bean" },
		{ "question": "隧道", "answers": [ "トンネル" ], "comment": "tunnel" },
		{ "question": "隼", "answers": [ "はやぶさ" ], "comment": "falcon (esp. the peregrine falcon, Falco peregrinus)" },
		{ "question": "雀", "answers": [ "すずめ" ], "comment": "tree sparrow (Passer montanus)\ntalkative person; knowledgeable person" },
		{ "question": "雀斑", "answers": [ "そばかす" ], "comment": "freckles" },
		{ "question": "雀蜂", "answers": [ "すずめばち" ], "comment": "hornet; yellow jacket; wasp (of subfamily Vespinae)\nAsian giant hornet (Vespa mandarinia); yak-killer hornet" },
		{ "question": "雀鷂", "answers": [ "つみ" ], "comment": "Japanese sparrowhawk (Accipiter gularis)" },
		{ "question": "雀鷹", "answers": [ "つみ" ], "comment": "Japanese sparrowhawk (Accipiter gularis)" },
		{ "question": "雁", "answers": [ "かり","かりがね" ], "comment": "wild goose\nglans; head of a penis\ncall of a wild goose\nwild goose (esp. a lesser white-fronted goose, Anser erythropus)\ntea made from twigs of high-quality tea plants (esp. gyokuro); high-grade kukicha (esp. from gyokuro)" },
		{ "question": "雁金", "answers": [ "かりがね" ], "comment": "call of a wild goose\nwild goose (esp. a lesser white-fronted goose, Anser erythropus)\ntea made from twigs of high-quality tea plants (esp. gyokuro); high-grade kukicha (esp. from gyokuro)" },
		{ "question": "雅典", "answers": [ "アテネ" ]},
		{ "question": "雉", "answers": [ "きじ" ], "comment": "green pheasant (Phasianus versicolor); Japanese pheasant" },
		{ "question": "雉子", "answers": [ "きじ" ], "comment": "green pheasant (Phasianus versicolor); Japanese pheasant" },
		{ "question": "雎鳩", "answers": [ "みさご" ], "comment": "osprey (Pandion haliaetus); fish hawk" },
		{ "question": "雨虎", "answers": [ "あめふらし" ], "comment": "sea hare (esp. species Aplysia kurodai)" },
		{ "question": "雨降", "answers": [ "あめふらし" ], "comment": "rainfall; rainy weather\nsea hare (esp. species Aplysia kurodai)" },
		{ "question": "雪洞", "answers": [ "ぼんぼり" ], "comment": "snow cave\npaper-covered lamp or lantern" },
		{ "question": "雪隠金亀子", "answers": [ "せんちこがね" ], "comment": "dor beetle (of family Geotrupidae)\nGeotrupes laevistriatus (species of dor beetle)" },
		{ "question": "雫", "answers": [ "しずく" ], "comment": "drop (of water); drip" },
		{ "question": "雲呑", "answers": [ "わんたん" ], "comment": "wonton (Chinese dumpling); won ton; wantan; wanton; wuntun" },
		{ "question": "雲脂", "answers": [ "ふけ" ], "comment": "dandruff" },
		{ "question": "雲雀", "answers": [ "ひばり" ], "comment": "skylark (Alauda arvensis)\nMongolian lark (Melanocorypha mongolica)" },
		{ "question": "雷魚", "answers": [ "はたはた" ], "comment": "sailfin sandfish (Arctoscopus japonicus); Japanese sandfish\nblotched snakehead (species of fish, Channa maculata)\nnorthern snakehead (species of fish, Channa argus)" },
		{ "question": "雹", "answers": [ "ひょう" ], "comment": "hail (esp. hailballs 5 mm or greater)" },
		{ "question": "電", "answers": [ "いなずま" ], "comment": "lightning; flash of lightning; lightning bolt" },
		{ "question": "霙", "answers": [ "みぞれ" ], "comment": "sleet (mixture of snow and rain)\nshaved ice topped with honey" },
		{ "question": "霞", "answers": [ "かすみ" ], "comment": "haze (esp. in spring); mist\ndimness (of sight)" },
		{ "question": "霰", "answers": [ "あられ" ], "comment": "hail (esp. hailballs under 5 mm); graupel\ndicing; small cubes\nroasted mochi pieces (usu. flavoured with soy sauce, etc.)" },
		{ "question": "露西亜", "answers": [ "ロシア" ], "comment": "Russia" },
		{ "question": "靄", "answers": [ "もや" ], "comment": "mist; haze" },
		{ "question": "青竜蝦", "answers": [ "しゃこ" ], "comment": "mantis shrimp (any marine crustacean of order Stomatopoda, esp. the species Oratosquilla oratoria)" },
		{ "question": "靨", "answers": [ "えくぼ" ], "comment": "dimple" },
		{ "question": "靫葛", "answers": [ "うつぼかずら" ], "comment": "pitcher plant" },
		{ "question": "韭", "answers": [ "にら" ], "comment": "Chinese chive; garlic chive (Allium tuberosum)" },
		{ "question": "韮", "answers": [ "にら" ], "comment": "Chinese chive; garlic chive (Allium tuberosum)" },
		{ "question": "音呼", "answers": [ "いんこ" ], "comment": "true parrot (esp. small parrots such as the parakeet, lory and conure)" },
		{ "question": "頁", "answers": [ "ページ" ], "comment": "page\nkanji \"big shell\" radical" },
		{ "question": "頭垢", "answers": [ "ふけ" ], "comment": "dandruff" },
		{ "question": "顋", "answers": [ "えら" ], "comment": "chin; jaw\ngills; branchia\nangle of the mandible; gonial angle" },
		{ "question": "風信子", "answers": [ "ヒヤシンス" ], "comment": "hyacinth (Hyacinthus orientalis)" },
		{ "question": "風琴", "answers": [ "オルガン" ], "comment": "organ; harmonium" },
		{ "question": "飛白", "answers": [ "かすり" ], "comment": "splash pattern (e.g. on a kimono); dye pattern; kasuri" },
		{ "question": "飛竜頭", "answers": [ "ヒリョウズ" ], "comment": "filhos (traditional Portuguese dessert)\ndeep-fried tofu mixed with thinly sliced vegetables" },
		{ "question": "飛蝗", "answers": [ "ばった" ], "comment": "grasshopper; locust (of superfamily Acridoidea)\nlocust swarming; locust swarm; (swarming) locusts" },
		{ "question": "食火鶏", "answers": [ "ひくいどり" ], "comment": "cassowary (Casuarius spp.)" },
		{ "question": "食蟻獣", "answers": [ "ありくい" ], "comment": "anteater" },
		{ "question": "飯匙倩", "answers": [ "はぶ" ], "comment": "habu (Trimeresurus flavoviridis); yellow-spotted pit viper" },
		{ "question": "飴坊", "answers": [ "あめんぼ" ], "comment": "pond skater (any insect of family Gerridae); water strider" },
		{ "question": "餃子", "answers": [ "ギョーザ" ], "comment": "gyoza; pot sticker; crescent-shaped pan-fried dumplings stuffed with minced pork and vegetables" },
		{ "question": "饂飩", "answers": [ "わんたん" ], "comment": "wonton (Chinese dumpling); won ton; wantan; wanton; wuntun\nudon; thick Japanese wheat noodles" },
		{ "question": "香蕈", "answers": [ "しいたけ" ], "comment": "shiitake mushroom (Lentinula edodes)" },
		{ "question": "香魚", "answers": [ "あゆ" ], "comment": "sweetfish (Plecoglossus altivelis altivelis); ayu\nsalmon" },
		{ "question": "馬克斯", "answers": [ "マルクス" ]},
		{ "question": "馬哈黙", "answers": [ "マホメット" ]},
		{ "question": "馬大頭", "answers": [ "おにやんま" ], "comment": "Siebold's dragonfly (Anotogaster sieboldii); jumbo dragonfly" },
		{ "question": "馬尼剌", "answers": [ "マニラ" ]},
		{ "question": "馬徳里", "answers": [ "マドリード" ], "comment": "Madrid" },
		{ "question": "馬来", "answers": [ "マライ", "マレー" ]},
		{ "question": "馬穴", "answers": [ "バケツ" ]},
		{ "question": "馬耳塞", "answers": [ "マルセイユ" ]},
		{ "question": "馬酔木", "answers": [ "あせび" ], "comment": "Japanese andromeda (Pieris japonica); lily-of-the-valley" },
		{ "question": "馬鈴薯", "answers": [ "ばれいしょ" ], "comment": "potato (Solanum tuberosum)" },
		{ "question": "馬陸", "answers": [ "やすで" ], "comment": "millipede" },
		{ "question": "馴鹿", "answers": [ "トナカイ" ], "comment": "reindeer (Rangifer tarandus)" },
		{ "question": "駄津", "answers": [ "だつ" ], "comment": "Pacific needlefish (Strongylura anastomella)" },
		{ "question": "駝鳥", "answers": [ "だちょう" ], "comment": "ostrich (Struthio camelus)" },
		{ "question": "駱駝", "answers": [ "らくだ" ], "comment": "camel\ncamel (cloth); cloth made from camel hair\ncamel (color); light yellowish brown" },
		{ "question": "騾馬", "answers": [ "らば" ], "comment": "mule" },
		{ "question": "驢馬", "answers": [ "ろば" ], "comment": "donkey; ass" },
		{ "question": "骨牌", "answers": [ "カルタ" ], "comment": "karuta; traditional Japanese playing cards\nplaying cards\nmahjong tiles made of animal bone" },
		{ "question": "骰子", "answers": [ "さいころ" ], "comment": "dice; die" },
		{ "question": "高加索", "answers": [ "コーカサス" ]},
		{ "question": "髪切虫", "answers": [ "かみきりむし" ], "comment": "long-horned beetle" },
		{ "question": "鬱金香", "answers": [ "チューリップ" ], "comment": "tulip" },
		{ "question": "鬼灯", "answers": [ "ほおずき" ], "comment": "ground cherry (Physalis alkekengi var. franchetii); husk tomato; Chinese lantern plant" },
		{ "question": "魚蝨", "answers": [ "ちょう" ]},
		{ "question": "鮃", "answers": [ "ひらめ" ], "comment": "flounder (esp. the large-tooth flounders of family Paralichthyidae, but also lefteye flounders of family Bothidae)\nbastard halibut; olive flounder (Paralichthys olivaceus)" },
		{ "question": "鮎", "answers": [ "あゆ" ], "comment": "sweetfish (Plecoglossus altivelis altivelis); ayu\nsalmon" },
		{ "question": "鮎並", "answers": [ "あいなめ" ], "comment": "fat greenling (Hexagrammos otakii)" },
		{ "question": "鮎魚女", "answers": [ "あいなめ" ], "comment": "fat greenling (Hexagrammos otakii)" },
		{ "question": "鮑", "answers": [ "あわび" ], "comment": "abalone; ear shell" },
		{ "question": "鮒", "answers": [ "ふな" ], "comment": "crucian carp (Carassius spp.)" },
		{ "question": "鮟鱇", "answers": [ "あんこう" ], "comment": "goosefish (any anglerfish of family Lophiidae); monkfish; sea devil\nfool\ncurved gutter\npotbellied sumo wrestler; wrestler with a big belly\ngoosefish (any anglerfish of family Lophiidae); monkfish; sea devil" },
		{ "question": "鮪", "answers": [ "まぐろ" ], "comment": "tuna (edible fish, Thunnus spp.); tunny\nPacific bluefin tuna (edible fish, Thunnus orientalis)\ndead lay; starfish; person who is inactive during sexual intercourse" },
		{ "question": "鮫", "answers": [ "さめ" ], "comment": "shark" },
		{ "question": "鮭", "answers": [ "さけ" ], "comment": "salmon (Salmonidae spp.)\nchum salmon (Oncorhynchus keta)" },
		{ "question": "鮴", "answers": [ "ごり" ], "comment": "fish of the genus Rhinogobius\ndusky tripletooth goby (Tridentiger obscurus)\ncommon freshwater goby (Gymnogobius urotaenia)\nJapanese fluvial sculpin (fish, Cottus pollux)" },
		{ "question": "鮹", "answers": [ "たこ" ], "comment": "octopus" },
		{ "question": "鯉", "answers": [ "こい" ], "comment": "common carp (Cyprinus carpio); koi carp" },
		{ "question": "鯊", "answers": [ "はぜ" ], "comment": "goby (fish)\nyellowfin goby (Acanthogobius flavimanus)" },
		{ "question": "鯒", "answers": [ "こち" ], "comment": "flathead (esp. the bartailed flathead, Platycephalus indicus)" },
		{ "question": "鯔", "answers": [ "ぼら" ], "comment": "striped mullet (Mugil cephalus)\nredlip mullet (Chelon haematocheilus)\nyoung striped mullet\nadult striped mullet\nin the end; after all is said and done" },
		{ "question": "鯖", "answers": [ "さば" ], "comment": "mackerel (esp. the chub mackerel, Scomber japonicus)\nserver (in an online game)" },
		{ "question": "鯛", "answers": [ "たい" ], "comment": "sea bream (Sparidae); porgy\ntai (species of reddish-brown Pacific sea bream, Pagrus major)" },
		{ "question": "鯡", "answers": [ "にしん" ], "comment": "Pacific herring (Clupea pallasii)" },
		{ "question": "鯨", "answers": [ "くじら" ], "comment": "whale (Cetacea spp.)" },
		{ "question": "鯰", "answers": [ "なまず" ], "comment": "catfish (esp. the Amur catfish, Silurus asotus)\nearthquake" },
		{ "question": "鯱", "answers": [ "しゃち" ], "comment": "orca (Orcinus orca); killer whale; grampus\nmythical carp with the head of a lion and the body of a fish (auspicious protectors of well-being)\nmythical carp with the head of a lion and the body of a fish (auspicious protectors of well-being)" },
		{ "question": "鰆", "answers": [ "さわら" ], "comment": "Japanese Spanish mackerel (Scomberomorus niphonius)" },
		{ "question": "鰈", "answers": [ "かれい" ], "comment": "righteye flounder (any fish of family Pleuronectidae)" },
		{ "question": "鰊", "answers": [ "にしん" ], "comment": "Pacific herring (Clupea pallasii)" },
		{ "question": "鰌", "answers": [ "どじょう" ], "comment": "loach (any fish of family Cobitidae)\nweather loach (Misgurnus anguillicaudatus)" },
		{ "question": "鰍", "answers": [ "かじか" ], "comment": "sculpin (any fish of family Cottidae, incl. the bullheads and the miller's-thumb)\nJapanese fluvial sculpin (Cottus pollux)\nyoung Japanese amberjack (Seriola quinqueradiata)" },
		{ "question": "鰐", "answers": [ "わに" ], "comment": "crocodile; alligator; crocodilian\nshark" },
		{ "question": "鰒", "answers": [ "ふぐ","あわび" ], "comment": "puffer fish; blow fish; fugu; globefish; swellfish\nabalone; ear shell" },
		{ "question": "鰓", "answers": [ "えら" ], "comment": "gills; branchia\nangle of the mandible; gonial angle\nchin; jaw\ngills; branchia" },
		{ "question": "鰡", "answers": [ "ぼら" ], "comment": "striped mullet (Mugil cephalus)\nredlip mullet (Chelon haematocheilus)" },
		{ "question": "鰤", "answers": [ "ぶり" ], "comment": "Japanese amberjack (species of yellowtail, Seriola quinqueradiata)" },
		{ "question": "鰭足鷸", "answers": [ "ひれあし" ], "comment": "phalarope (any sandpiper of family Phalaropodidae)" },
		{ "question": "鰮", "answers": [ "いわし" ], "comment": "pilchard (esp. Japanese pilchard, Sardinops melanostictus); sardine (esp. sardine of Japanese pilchard)" },
		{ "question": "鰯", "answers": [ "いわし" ], "comment": "pilchard (esp. Japanese pilchard, Sardinops melanostictus); sardine (esp. sardine of Japanese pilchard)" },
		{ "question": "鰰", "answers": [ "はたはた" ], "comment": "sailfin sandfish (Arctoscopus japonicus); Japanese sandfish" },
		{ "question": "鰹", "answers": [ "かつお" ], "comment": "skipjack tuna (Katsuwonus pelamis); oceanic bonito; victorfish" },
		{ "question": "鰹鳥", "answers": [ "かつおどり" ], "comment": "booby (esp. the brown booby, Sula leucogaster); gannet" },
		{ "question": "鰺刺", "answers": [ "あじさし" ], "comment": "tern (esp. the common tern, Sterna hirundo)" },
		{ "question": "鰺（鯵）", "answers": [ "あじ" ], "comment": "horse mackerel (Carangidae spp., esp. the Japanese horse mackerel, Trachurus japonicus); jack mackerel; pompano; scad" },
		{ "question": "鰻", "answers": [ "うなぎ" ], "comment": "eel (esp. the Japanese eel, Anguilla japonica)\neel (esp. the Japanese eel, Anguilla japonica)" },
		{ "question": "鱈", "answers": [ "たら" ], "comment": "gadid (any fish of the family Gadidae, incl. cod, haddock, whiting and pollack)\nPacific cod (Gadus macrocephalus)" },
		{ "question": "鱒", "answers": [ "ます" ], "comment": "trout; sea trout" },
		{ "question": "鱚", "answers": [ "きす" ], "comment": "sillago (any fish of genus Sillago, esp. the Japanese whiting, Sillago japonica)" },
		{ "question": "鱧", "answers": [ "はも" ], "comment": "daggertooth pike conger (Muraenesox cinereus)\n(in Northern Japan) conger eel; garden eel" },
		{ "question": "鱶", "answers": [ "ふか" ], "comment": "(large) shark" },
		{ "question": "鱸", "answers": [ "すずき" ], "comment": "Japanese sea perch (Lateolabrax japonicus, esp. referring to an adult); Japanese sea bass" },
		{ "question": "鳥兜", "answers": [ "とりかぶと" ], "comment": "aconite (esp. species Aconitum japonicum); wolfsbane; monkshood\ntraditional bugaku hat" },
		{ "question": "鳥甲", "answers": [ "とりかぶと" ], "comment": "aconite (esp. species Aconitum japonicum); wolfsbane; monkshood\ntraditional bugaku hat" },
		{ "question": "鳧", "answers": [ "かも" ], "comment": "duck\neasy mark; sucker; sitting duck\ngray-headed lapwing (Microsarcops cinereus); grey-headed lapwing" },
		{ "question": "鳩", "answers": [ "はと" ], "comment": "pigeon; dove" },
		{ "question": "鳩尾", "answers": [ "みぞおち" ], "comment": "pit of the stomach; solar plexus" },
		{ "question": "鳳梨", "answers": [ "パイナップル" ], "comment": "pineapple" },
		{ "question": "鳳蝶", "answers": [ "あげはちょう" ], "comment": "swallowtail butterfly (esp. the citrus swallowtail butterfly, Papilio xuthus)" },
		{ "question": "鳶", "answers": [ "とび" ], "comment": "black kite (Milvus migrans)\nconstruction worker; scaffold erector; firefighter\nInverness cape" },
		{ "question": "鴇", "answers": [ "とき" ], "comment": "Japanese crested ibis (Nipponia nippon); crested ibis\nbustard (esp. the great bustard, Otis tarda)" },
		{ "question": "鴈", "answers": [ "かり" ], "comment": "wild goose\nglans; head of a penis" },
		{ "question": "鴉", "answers": [ "からす" ], "comment": "crow (Corvus spp.); raven" },
		{ "question": "鴎", "answers": [ "かもめ" ], "comment": "common gull (Larus canus); mew gull\ngull (Laridae spp.); seagull" },
		{ "question": "鴛鴦", "answers": [ "おしどり" ], "comment": "mandarin duck" },
		{ "question": "鴟", "answers": [ "とび" ], "comment": "black kite (Milvus migrans)\nconstruction worker; scaffold erector; firefighter\nInverness cape" },
		{ "question": "鴨", "answers": [ "かも" ], "comment": "duck\neasy mark; sucker; sitting duck" },
		{ "question": "鴫", "answers": [ "しぎ" ], "comment": "sandpiper (any bird of family Scolopacidae, incl. the curlews, godwits, phalaropes, redshanks, ruff, snipes, turnstones, and woodcocks)" },
		{ "question": "鴻", "answers": [ "ひしくい" ], "comment": "bean goose (Anser fabalis)\nlarge bird\npeng (in Chinese mythology, giant bird said to transform from a fish)\nfenghuang (Chinese phoenix)" },
		{ "question": "鴿", "answers": [ "はと" ], "comment": "pigeon; dove\ndomestic pigeon; feral pigeon" },
		{ "question": "鵄", "answers": [ "とび" ], "comment": "black kite (Milvus migrans)\nconstruction worker; scaffold erector; firefighter\nInverness cape" },
		{ "question": "鵆", "answers": [ "ちどり" ], "comment": "plover" },
		{ "question": "鵙", "answers": [ "もず" ], "comment": "shrike (any bird of family Laniidae)\nbull-headed shrike (Lanius bucephalus); butcher bird" },
		{ "question": "鵜", "answers": [ "う" ], "comment": "cormorant (Phalacrocoracidae spp.)" },
		{ "question": "鶉", "answers": [ "うずら" ], "comment": "quail\nJapanese quail (Coturnix japonica)" },
		{ "question": "鶏", "answers": [ "にわとり" ], "comment": "(domestic) chicken\nchicken (meat)" },
		{ "question": "鶚", "answers": [ "みさご" ], "comment": "osprey (Pandion haliaetus); fish hawk" },
		{ "question": "鶩", "answers": [ "あひる" ], "comment": "domestic duck" },
		{ "question": "鶫", "answers": [ "つぐみ" ], "comment": "thrush (esp. the dusky thrush, Turdus naumanni)" },
		{ "question": "鶯", "answers": [ "うぐいす" ], "comment": "Japanese bush warbler (Horornis diphone); Japanese nightingale\ngreenish brown\nhaving a beautiful voice" },
		{ "question": "鶴", "answers": [ "つる" ], "comment": "crane (any bird of the family Gruidae, esp. the red-crowned crane, Grus japonensis)" },
		{ "question": "鷲", "answers": [ "わし" ], "comment": "eagle (Accipitridae family)" },
		{ "question": "鷸", "answers": [ "しぎ" ], "comment": "sandpiper (any bird of family Scolopacidae, incl. the curlews, godwits, phalaropes, redshanks, ruff, snipes, turnstones, and woodcocks)" },
		{ "question": "鷹", "answers": [ "たか" ], "comment": "falcon (Falconidae spp.); hawk" },
		{ "question": "鷺", "answers": [ "さぎ" ], "comment": "heron (Ardeidae)" },
		{ "question": "鷺草", "answers": [ "さぎそう" ], "comment": "fringed orchid (Pecteilis radiata); white egret flower; sagiso" },
		{ "question": "鸚哥", "answers": [ "いんこ" ], "comment": "true parrot (esp. small parrots such as the parakeet, lory and conure)" },
		{ "question": "鸚鵡", "answers": [ "おうむ" ], "comment": "(large) parrot (incl. the cockatoo)" },
		{ "question": "鸚鵡貝", "answers": [ "おうむがい" ], "comment": "chambered nautilus (esp. species Nautilus pompilius)" },
		{ "question": "鸛", "answers": [ "こうのとり" ], "comment": "stork (esp. the Oriental stork, Ciconia boyciana)" },
		{ "question": "鹿尾菜", "answers": [ "ひじき" ], "comment": "hijiki (dark edible seaweed usu. sold in dried black strips; Hizikia fusiformis)" },
		{ "question": "麒麟", "answers": [ "きりん" ], "comment": "giraffe (Giraffa camelopardalis)\nqilin (Chinese unicorn)\nKirin (brand of beer)" },
		{ "question": "麝香猫", "answers": [ "じゃこうねこ" ], "comment": "civet cat" },
		{ "question": "麦唐納", "answers": [ "マクドナルド" ]},
		{ "question": "麦酒", "answers": [ "ビール" ], "comment": "beer" },
		{ "question": "麺麭", "answers": [ "パン" ], "comment": "bread" },
		{ "question": "黄楊", "answers": [ "つげ" ], "comment": "Japanese box tree (Buxus microphylla var. japonica); Japanese boxwood" },
		{ "question": "黄櫨", "answers": [ "はぜのき" ], "comment": "wax tree (Toxicodendron succedaneum); Japanese wax tree" },
		{ "question": "黄瓜", "answers": [ "きゅうり" ], "comment": "cucumber (Cucumis sativus)" },
		{ "question": "黄葉", "answers": [ "もみじ" ], "comment": "autumn colours; fall colors; leaves changing color (colour)\nleaves turning yellow; yellow leaves\n(Japanese) maple (Acer japonicum)\nvenison" },
		{ "question": "黄蜀葵", "answers": [ "とろろあおい" ], "comment": "sunset hibiscus (Hibiscus manihot)" },
		{ "question": "黄金虫", "answers": [ "こがねむし" ], "comment": "scarabaeid beetle\nMimela splendens (metallic-green scarabaeid beetle)" },
		{ "question": "黄鼬", "answers": [ "てん" ], "comment": "Japanese marten (Martes melampus)\nmarten (any arboreal weasel-like mammal of genus Martes)" },
		{ "question": "黍", "answers": [ "きび" ], "comment": "(common) millet (Panicum miliaceium); proso millet" },
		{ "question": "黒子", "answers": [ "ほくろ" ], "comment": "stage assistant dressed in black (in kabuki); stagehand; prompter\nbehind-the-scenes supporter; string-puller\ndark mole; facial mole; beauty spot" },
		{ "question": "黒死病", "answers": [ "ペスト" ], "comment": "bubonic plague; black death" },
		{ "question": "黴", "answers": [ "かび" ], "comment": "mold; mould; mildew" },
		{ "question": "黴菌", "answers": [ "ばいきん" ], "comment": "germ; germs; bacteria; mold; mould\nsomething harmful; vermin" },
		{ "question": "黶", "answers": [ "あざ","ほくろ" ], "comment": "birthmark; nevus\nbruise" },
		{ "question": "鼈", "answers": [ "すっぽん" ], "comment": "Chinese soft-shelled turtle (Pelodiscus sinensis); soft-shelled turtle (Trionychidae)" },
		{ "question": "鼠", "answers": [ "ねずみ" ], "comment": "mouse; rat\ndark gray; dark grey; slate (color, colour)" },
		{ "question": "鼬", "answers": [ "いたち" ], "comment": "weasel (esp. the Japanese weasel, Mustela itatsi)\nmustelid (any other member of the weasel family, incl. badgers, martens, minks, ferrets, otters, polecats, stoats, skunks, etc.)" },
		{ "question": "鼬魚", "answers": [ "いたちうお" ], "comment": "goatsbeard brotula (species of ophidiiform fish, Brotula multibarbata)" },
		{ "question": "鼬鼠", "answers": [ "いたち" ], "comment": "weasel (esp. the Japanese weasel, Mustela itatsi)\nmustelid (any other member of the weasel family, incl. badgers, martens, minks, ferrets, otters, polecats, stoats, skunks, etc.)" },
		{ "question": "鼾", "answers": [ "いびき" ], "comment": "snoring; snore" }
	]
}
